♪ IN THE NOT-TOO-DISTANT
FUTURE ♪
♪ NEXT SUNDAY, A.D. ♪
♪ THERE WAS A GUY
NAMED JOEL ♪
♪ NOT TOO DIFFERENT
FROM YOU OR ME ♪
♪ HE WORKED
AT GIZMONIC INSTITUTE ♪
♪ JUST ANOTHER FACE
IN A RED JUMPSUIT ♪
♪ HE DID A GOOD JOB
CLEANING UP THE PLACE ♪
♪ BUT HIS BOSSES
DIDN'T LIKE HIM ♪
♪ SO THEY SHOT HIM
INTO SPACE ♪
♪♪
♪ WE'LL SEND HIM
CHEESY MOVIES ♪
♪ THE WORST WE CAN FIND
LA LA LA ♪
♪ HE'LL HAVE TO SIT
AND WATCH THEM ALL ♪
♪ AND THE MONITOR IS MINE
LA LA LA ♪
♪ NOW KEEP IN MIND
JOEL CAN'T CONTROL ♪
♪ WHERE THE MOVIES BEGIN OR END
LA LA LA ♪
♪ BECAUSE HE USED
THOSE SPECIAL PARTS ♪
♪ TO MAKE HIS ROBOT FRIENDS ♪
ROBOT ROLL CALL:
CAMBOT,
- GYPSY...
- HI, GIRLS.
- ... TOM SERVO...
- WHAT A COOL GUY.
- ... CROW!
- WHAT A WISECRACKER.
♪ IF YOU'RE WONDERING HOW
HE EATS AND BREATHES ♪
♪ AND OTHER SCIENCE FACTS
LA LA LA ♪
♪ THEN REPEAT TO YOURSELF
IT'S JUST A SHOW ♪
♪ I SHOULD REALLY
JUST RELAX ♪
♪ FOR MYSTERY SCIENCE THEATER ♪
♪ 3000 ♪♪
I REALLY THINK
THIS IS GOING TO BE IT.
THIS IS MY YEAR.
YOU SAY THAT EVERY YEAR
WE GO
TO THE MAD SCIENTISTS
CONVENTION.
AH, BUT THIS YEAR
IS DIFFERENT.
THEY LAUGHED WHEN I MADE
THE MORE-PAINFUL MOUSETRAP,
BUT MY ENTRANCE INTO
THE MAD SCIENTIST COMPETITION
IS GOING TO MAKE ME FAMOUS.
- INFAMOUS.
- AH, THAT TOO, THAT TOO.
OKAY, PROMISE ME, IF YOU LOSE
THE CONTEST THIS YEAR,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BLOW UP THE
WHOLE CONVENTION CENTER AGAIN.
I ONLY DID THAT ONCE.
OH, UH...UH...
OKAY, TWICE, TWICE.
IT WAS TWICE.
IT WAS THREE TIMES!
THE THIRD TIME I USED
THE INCENDIARIES,
AND IT DIDN'T ACTUALLY
MAKE THE BUILDING BLOW UP,
IT JUST MADE IT BURN
REALLY QUICKLY.
GOD, THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL,
WASN'T IT?
OKAY, I'll GIVE YOU THAT.
OH, IT'S TIME
TO CALL JOEL NOW.
THE EXPERIMENT HAS TO START.
RIGHT, RIGHT,
I KNOW THAT.
COME IN, JOELENE, YOU
FREE-FLOATING SPACE FERRET.
WELL, SIRS, I'M READY
FOR THIS WEEK'S
INVENTION EXCHANGE.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY HAVE
AIRBAGS FOR CARS?
BUT THEY HAVEN'T INVENTED
ANYTHING YET
FOR US MOTORCYCLISTS,
SO I CAME UP WITH THIS--
THE AIRBAG HELMET.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, GREAT, GET RALPH NADER
ON THE PHONE.
AND THEN CALL
GARY BUSEY.
- IS IT OUR TURN NOW?
- YES.
OKAY, THIS IS OUR INVENTION
FOR THIS WEEK.
IT'S CALLED THE CHALKMAN.
YES, WE'RE ENTERING THIS
IN THE MAD SCIENTIST COMPETITION
THIS YEAR.
OH, WE HAVE OTHER CHOICES,
BUT THIS IS THE ONE
WE'RE GOING WITH.
THIS IS VERY STRONG.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY,
YOU'RE THROWING A PARTY,
IT'S 3:00 A.M., AND NONE
OF THE GUESTS ARE LEAVING.
THAT'S WHEN YOU BRING OUT
THE CHALKMAN.
YES, AS EVERY SELF-RESPECTING
SCIENTIST KNOWS,
THE SOUND OF HUMAN FINGERNAILS
ON A CHALKBOARD
IS MOST ANNOYING.
IT INITIATES THE PRIMAL FEAR
RESPONSE IN ALL MAMMALS.
MUCH LIKE A CHIMPANZEE
SCURRYING ACROSS THE PLAINS
OF THE SERENGETI IN FEAR.
SIMPLY PUT YOUR CHALKMAN
ON THE PLATEN.
- THIS IS A REAL CHALKBOARD
- PUT ON SIDE "B".
SIDE "B".
EXCELLENT.
AND JUST, YOU'LL NOTICE,
THE TONEARM HAS
REAL HUMAN FINGERNAILS
EMBEDDED IN THE HAND.
NOW PLACE IT ON THE PLATEN...
[HORRIBLE FINGERNAIL
SCREECHING]
... OH...
OPEN IT.
- THEY'LL STAY.
- CLOSE IT.
[SCREECHING]
THEY LEAVE.
- OPEN IT.
- THEY'LL STAY.
- CLOSE IT.
- THEY'LL LEAVE.
- OPEN IT.
- STAY.
AND SO ON AND SO ON
AND SO ON.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THAT, JOEL-MEISTER?
- WOW, IT'S REALLY ANNOYING.
- [BOTH]
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT'S
THIS WEEK'S EXPERIMENT?
IT'S CALLED "THE ROBOT VS.
THE AZTEC MUMMY,"
AND IT'S ALMOST AS ANNOYING
AS THIS CHALKMAN HERE.
YES, BUT FIRST WE'RE GOING
TO SCOUR YOUR PALATE
WITH A LITTLE CINEMATIC
SCIENCE FICTION SORBET.
IT'S AN OLD SERIAL CALLED
"COMMANDO CODY
AND THE ROCKET MEN
FROM THE MOON."
UH, BE CAREFUL, LARRY,
I'VE INSTALLED
A NEW SECURITY SYSTEM HERE
IN DEEP 13,
SO BE CAREFUL
WHICH BUTTONS YOU PUSH
ON THE PANEL, ALL RIGHT?
NEAT-O, OKAY,
HOW DOES IT WORK?
OH, WELL, STAND OVER THERE
ON THAT MARK
AND PRETEND
YOU'RE FROM ACCOUNTING.
OKAY.
YOU MEAN THIS MARK HERE?
- YES.
- OH---
HMM, INTERESTING.
HERE--
HERE'S YOUR MOVIE, JOEL.
[ALARM BUZZING]
MOVIE SIGN!
♪♪
AW, YOU'RE GETTING TO HEAVY.
- A REPUBLIC SERIAL.
- YEAH.
YOU EVER HEARD
OF SERIALS BEFORE?
YEAH, LIGHT OAT.
OH, LOOK, IT'S PUMPKIN BOY.
NO, IT'S NOT THAT KIND
OF SERIAL.
- SO IT MEANS, A, UH--
- OH, SO IT'S A WHEAT THING?
NO, A MOVIE THAT'S
IN SERIES.
- WHAT?
- OH, YOU'LL CATCH ON.
IT'S NOT A WHOLE MOVIE.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE GO AND SEE
PART OF A MOVIE?
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S ALWAYS A BORING SHORT.
- YEAH.
- MY SHORTS ARE NEVER BORING.
THANK YOU, TOM.
♪♪
IS THE MUSIC ALWAYS
THIS POOR IN SERIALS?
[JOEL LAUGHS]
YES.
I'M THINKING I MIGHT
GET IT THEN.
HE'S THE HEAVY.
YOU CAN TELL WHEN
THE MUSIC SWELLS UP.
ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
[EXPLOSION]
I GUESS THAT'S THE END
OF CHAPTER ONE.
[TOM, IMITATING NARRATOR]
OKLAHOMA, 1934.
THE OIL FIELDS ARE ABLAZE.
♪♪
[EXPLOSION]
HOLY...
HEY, LOOK, THERE'S A SALE
AT PENNY'S.
"BIG STUFF BLOWING UP
EVERYWHERE."
MAYBE IT'S A FIRE SALE.
[TOM CHUCKLES]
♪♪
"NEW PETITION
AGAINST TAX LAW."
"THE CONTINUED WAVE
OF DEATH-DEALING EXPLOSIONS
"STRUCK YESTERDAY
AT AREA DEFENSE HEADQUARTERS.
"AS ON PREVIOUS OCCASIONS,
THE AUTHORITIES ARE UNABLE
"TO DETECT THE CAUSE
OF THESE BLASTS,
WHICH HAVE DONE UNTOLD DAMAGE."
WHO'S THAT GUY
MIXING DRINKS.
UH, PROFESSOR TOM COLLINS.
WELL, THERE ARE SEVERAL
THEORIES, JOAN,
BUT SO FAR,
NO ONE IS EVEN SURE
WHAT KIND OF EXPLOSIVES
ARE BEING USED
OR HOW THEY'RE SET OFF.
MAYBE MR. HENDERSON WILL HAVE
SOME INFORMATION FOR US
WHEN HE GETS IN
FROM WASHINGTON.
THAT GUY HENDERSON WOULDN'T
TELL YOU WHAT TIME IT IS.
JUST WHAT IS HIS JOB,
ANYWAY?
MAYBE HE DOESN'T HAVE A WATCH.
HE ONLY ANSWERS TO A FEW PEOPLE
IN THIS COUNTRY OF OURS.
I THINK THAT--
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
AND THEY'RE ALL NAMED SUE.
- HELLO, MR. HENDERSON.
- HELLO, COMMANDER CODY.
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
- TED, MISS GILBERT.
HOW ARE YOU GETTING ALONG
WITH THE ROCKET SHIP?
AS WELL AS CAN BE
EXPECTED, SIR.
OUR TESTS WITH THE MODEL
ARE SATISFACTORY.
IF THE GOVERNMENT WOULD LET US
MAKE A FEW TEST FLIGHTS
WITH THE ROCKET--
IT'S OUT OF THE QUESTION.
THIS WHOLE PROJECT'S
STRICTLY TOP SECRET.
SINCE YOU PEOPLE DEVELOPED
THE ROCKET SHIP FOR US
AND WE'LL BE THE ONES
OPERATING IT,
IT HAS BEEN DECIDED THAT YOU
SHOULD KNOW MORE OF OUR PLANS.
GEE, NICE HEAD.
I'VE BEEN AUTHORIZED
TO TELL YOU THIS MUCH.
ITS PRIMARY USE WILL BE
TO COMBAT THIS WAVE
OF SABOTAGE AND DESTRUCTION
OF OUR DEFENSE SYSTEM.
DUH...
YOU MEAN THE GOVERNMENT KNOWS
WHAT'S CAUSING IT?
YEAH, THEY READ
THE PAPERS TOO.
TESTS OF THE WRECKAGE SHOW
THAT THE EXPLOSIONS
ARE OF ATOMIC ORIGIN.
YOU MEAN SOMEONE'S DROPPING
ATOMIC BOMBS ON US?
NOT BOMBS.
NO PLANES HAVE BEEN OBSERVED,
AND THE EXPLOSIONS AREN'T
SEVERE ENOUGH.
NO, FROM WHAT I'VE LEARNED
OF THE NATURE OF THE BLASTS,
THEY SEEM MORE LIKE
AN ATOMIC RAY OF SOME KIND.
OF COURSE,
THAT'S JUST A GUESS.
IT'S THE SAME GUESS
THAT WE'VE MADE
BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY
POSSIBLE ANSWER.
BUT NO ONE HAVE EVER
BEEN ABLE TO MAKE
AN ATOMIC RAY MACHINE.
YOU MEAN NO ONE ON EARTH
EVER HAS.
HUH?
SAY, THIS ROCKET
WE'RE BUILDING WILL BE ABLE
TO FLY TO THE MOON.
MAYBE SOMEONE UP THERE
HAS BUILT ONE
THAT COULD GET DOWN HERE.
WE BELIEVE THAT POSSIBLE.
AND FOR SOME TIME, OUR
ASTRONOMERS HAVE BEEN NOTICING
AN UNUSUAL AMOUNT
OF ATOMIC ACTIVITY ON THE MOON.
ISN'T ANY AMOUNT
OF ATOMIC ACTIVITY
ON THE MOON UNUSUAL?
ATOMIC BLASTS ON THE EARTH.
THE TWO KNOWN FACTS
FIT TOGETHER.
- YES, IT ADDS UP.
- LIKE A GROCERY BILL.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU WANT US
TO FLY TO THE MOON.
YES, AND WHEN YOU GET
TO THE MOON,
FIND OUT IF THESE ATTACKS
ARE ACTUALLY COMING FROM THERE.
AND BRING BACK SOME CHEESE.
AND TRY TO DEVISE SOME PLAN
FOR STOPPING THEM.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WE'LL DO WHAT WE CAN
WITH THESE ATTACKS HERE.
IS YOUR FLYING SUIT
STILL WORKING?
- NO, IT NEEDS TO BE LET OUT.
- YES.
WE MAY ASK YOU TO USE IT.
IF A RAY GUN IS BEING USED
TO CAUSE THESE BLASTS,
IT'S PROBABLY BEING OPERATED
FROM THE GROUND.
AND IF YOU COULD GET
TO THE SCENE OF THE ATTACK
SOON ENOUGH,
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE
TO FIND SOME CLUE
TO THE ATTACKERS.
- I'LL BE GLAD TO TRY.
- GOOD.
OR IF WE FIND OUT
WHAT TIME IT IS.
- ALL RIGHT, SIR.
- GOOD-BYE.
♪♪
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
THERE SHE IS,
RIGHT ON TIME.
IT'S A TRAIN, ALL RIGHT.
[EXPLOSION]
WHOA!
- FEELS GOOD, DON'T IT?
- THAT DID IT.
- NICE SHOOTING, LIONEL.
- THANKS, TYCO.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GET OUT THERE
RIGHT AWAY.
SAY, GIVE ME A HAND
WITH THE FLYING SUIT, TED.
YOU'RE GONNA WEAR THAT TIE
TO FLY IN?
... WAS BLASTED OUT
IN THE WEST END OF THE VALLEY.
A RANCHER REPORTED
HE SAW A TRUCK PARKED
ON A HILL
OVERLOOKING THE TRACKS
WITH TWO MEN IN IT
WORKING SOME KIND OF A GUN.
THEY PULLED OUT
RIGHT AFTER THE WRECK
AND HEADED TOWARD
KERN HILLS.
HENDERSON'S OFFICE GAVE ME
A DESCRIPTION OF THE TRUCK,
SO I'M GOING OUT
TO LOOK FOR IT.
I SUPPOSE YOU'LL BE
WANTING THIS.
YES, AND I'LL TAKE
THE GUN TOO.
I MAY NEED IT.
♪♪
GOOD LUCK,
PUMPKIN BOY.
TAKE YOUR PROTEIN PILLS
AND PUT YOUR HELMET ON.
- WINDOW!
- HEY, LOOK OUT!
- HELLO, WINDOW!
- BOY, THAT WAS CLOSE.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
OH... OH, MOMMY.
OH...
GOOD AFTERNOON,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
WE ARE CRUISING AT
APPROXIMATELY 50 FEET.
THE CAPTAIN HAS TURNED OFF
THE "NO SCREAMING" SIGN,
AND WE JUST EMPTIED
THE WASHROOM.
♪♪
LOOKS LIKE AN ATOMIC
NOSE HAIR CLIPPER.
WHY DO THEY HATE TRAINS
SO MUCH?
IT'S NOT SO MUCH
THAT THEY HATE TRAINS,
THEY HATE WHAT THEY
STAND FOR.
OH, THAT CLEARS
EVERYTHING UP.
WHOA.
GOING DOWN.
JANE, STOP THIS CRAZY THING!
UNH!
I THINK HE'S GOTTA
TAKE A LEAK.
LUCKILY, THEY WON'T SEE HIM.
NOW!
HE WAS CLEVERLY DISGUISED
AS A HERSHEY'S KISS.
I THINK HE'S JUST
DRAWN ATTENTION TO HIMSELF.
[JOEL CHUCKLES]
WHY DON'T THEY SHOOT HIM
WITH THE RAY GUN?
WELL, BECAUSE EVEN BACK THEN
IN THE MOVIES,
EVEN THE CROOKS HAD A SENSE
OF FAIR PLAY, TOM SERVO.
OKAY, UH, IT'S A SERIAL, JOEL,
NOT A MOVIE.
- RIGHT.
- A SERIAL!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- AND LEAVE THE RAY GUN?
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
[GUNSHOTS]
WELL, YOU COULD TAKE
THE TRUCK.
NAH.
MUCH BETTER TO RUN
IN THE DESERT ON FOOT,
WITH NO PROVISIONS
OR ANYTHING.
- AND EAT YOUR GUN.
- [JOEL CHUCKLES]
HEY, IT MATCHES MY HELMET
AND EVERYTHING.
ALL I NEED IS A SPARKMASTER
PLAY SET AND I'M DONE.
THE LOSS OF THE RAY GUN
IS NOT TOO SERIOUS.
I BROUGHT SUFFICIENT EQUIPMENT
FROM THE MOON
TO BUILD SEVERAL OF THEM.
BUT I DO NOT CARE
TO HAVE THE EARTH PEOPLE LEARN
THE SECRETS
OF OUR WEAPONS.
FROM THE DESCRIPTION
YOU GAVE ME
OF YOUR ATTACKER'S
COSTUME,
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
COMMANDO CODY
AND HIS FLYING SUIT.
OR A TRASHCAN HEAD.
HE WILL PROBABLY TAKE
OUR RAY GUN
TO HIS LABORATORY
FOR EXAMINATION,
SO YOU MUST GO THERE AT ONCE
AND RECOVER THE ATOMIC CHAMBER
FROM THE RAY GUN.
THAT'S A LARGE ORDER, KRUG.
WE HIRED OUT TO WORK YOUR
RAY GUN, BUT THIS BUSINESS--
YOU WERE HIRED TO DO ANYTHING
THAT I MAY CONSIDER NECESSARY
TO PAVE THE WAY FOR OUR
INVASION FROM THE MOON.
YOU'RE BEING WELL PAID
FOR YOUR WORK,
SO DO AS YOU'RE ORDERED.
YEAH, WELL PAID,
BUT IN MOON ROCKS.
MAYBE WE CAN AFFORD
ONE OF YOUR SUITS.
HEY, THIS LOOKS LIKE
THE RIGHT DOOR.
IS WORKING ON THIS GUN
GOING TO HOLD UP
FINISHING THE ROCKET SHIP?
- NO.
- MAYBE.
I'LL JUST GIVE IT
A QUICK EXAMINATION
AND THEN TURN IT OVER
TO THE AUTHORITIES.
WE'LL STILL BE ABLE TO TAKE OFF
FOR THE MOON NEXT WEDNESDAY.
♪♪
OH, I HAT TO SHOOT
A BUTT LIKE THAT.
[JOEL CHUCKLES]
TAKE IT EASY
AND YOU WON'T GET HURT.
MOVE BACK.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT MY
AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR SAID.
YEE-HAW!
GOOD THING SCIENTISTS ARE
SUCH GOOD FIGHTERS.
YEAH, SCIENTISTS VERSUS
HIRED THUGS--
GEEKS AND THUGS,
YOU GOTTA LOVE IT.
♪♪
[GUNSHOT]
BOY, THEY'RE USING A LOT
OF BREAKAWAY CHAIRS.
OH, I THOUGHT THAT WAS
A LOOSE STOOL.
AND THIS IS FOR
LOUIS PASTEUR!
NICE FALL.
EXCUSE ME,
MAY I CUT IN?
ANOTHER BLOW FOR SCIENCE.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE STRIKES--
YOU'RE OUTTA THERE.
ROUTINE 27.
AND DON'T TRY
TO FOLLOW US.
TELL YOUR FRIENDS.
HEY, THEY LEFT THE RAY GUN.
YEAH, BUT THEY TOOK
THE BATTERIES.
I DIDN'T KNOW
JACKIE GLEASON WAS IN THIS.
THEY'RE IN THE MIDDLE...
OF A GIANT CHESS GAME.
HMM, FRESH-GROUND PEPPER?
KRUG CALLING RETTIK.
LOOKS LIKE A PEPPERMILL.
- YOU SEE--
- YEAH.
- YEAH, GET IT?
- MM-HMM.
- I'M LAUGHING HARD INSIDE.
- COME IN, KRUG.
- THE ROCKET SHIP
IS LEAVING HERE
IN FIVE DAYS
TO INVESTIGATE OUR MOON.
I DID NOT BELIEVE THE EARTHMEN
POSSESSED A SHIP
CAPABLE OF MAKING
THE JOURNEY.
I JUST LEARNED
ABOUT IT MYSELF,
BUT I'M SURE MY INFORMATION
IS CORRECT.
STOP TALKING INTO
A SHOE BUFFER.
- WE WILL BE PREPARED...
- HE LOOKS LIKE WILLARD SCOTT.
AND DON'T FORGET THE CHEESE.
AND SPEAKING OF CHEESE...
OH, HOW I LOVE HIM.
♪♪
THEY'RE GONNA LAUNCH
FROM A MINIATURE GOLF COURSE?
BE FINE IF
THEY CLEAR THE WINDMILL.
I STILL THINK THIS IS
NO TRIP FOR A WOMAN.
NOW, DON'T START THAT AGAIN.
YOU'LL BE VERY GLAD
TO HAVE SOMEONE ALONG
WHO CAN COOK YOUR MEALS.
I'LL SAY WE WILL.
DON'T GIVE HER ANY...
YEAH, AND PRETTY SOON
I'LL BE ABLE TO VOTE.
I LIKE TO EAT TOO.
NICE ENSEMBLE,
ANYWAY.
ARE THE DICKS
COMING WITH US?
UH, NO, WE CALL THEM
POLICE OFFICERS NOW, DEAR.
OH, I DIDN'T KNOW.
I CAN'T EVEN VOTE.
WELL, THE BEST OF LUCK
TO ALL OF YOU, SIR.
HOPE THIS THING
WORKS ALL RIGHT.
SO DO WE.
GOOD-BYE.
GOOD-BYE, SIR.
WE'LL JUST WAIT BACK HERE WHERE
IT'S SAFE, BY THE THRUSTERS.
- HIYA, FOLKS.
- HELLO, HANK.
- ALL SET?
- ALL WARMED UP.
WE CAN TAKE OFF RIGHT NOW,
THAT IS, IF THE SHIP WILL
STAND UP THE TESTS WE MADE
WITH THE MODEL.
I THINK IT WILL.
NOW LET'S GO.
SAFETY BELTS FASTENED?
THEY'RE SITTING
IN OFFICE CHAIRS.
FIRE PILOT JETS.
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE
YOUR STAPLES.
LEAN BACK TO SIMULATE
G-FORCES.
- EVERYONE.
- FIRE MAIN JETS.
GOOD.
IN CASE OF AN EMERGENCY,
YOUR OFFICE CHAIR BECOMES
A FLOATATION DEVICE.
♪♪
WHY, YOU'D HARDLY KNOW
WE WERE MOVING.
WELL, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
WE ARE,
AT A LOT OF MILES PER MINUTE.
SHE'S LIVING UP
TO THE TESTS WE MADE.
- SET A COURSE FOR THE MOON.
- RIGHT.
"A LOT OF MILES PER MINUTE"?
HERE, FILE THIS,
I'M GOING TO THE WASHROOM.
HERE, SIT IN MY SEAT.
I WANNA PLAY WITH YOUR STUFF.
HEY, TRIPLE WORD SCORE!
HEY, IS THIS A CONTRACTION?
YOU CAN'T HYPHENATE.
YOU KNOW, I COULD MAKE IT
IN HALF THE TIME
IF I HAD A STRAIGHTEDGE.
SURE IS SUNNY IN SPACE.
WE'RE JUST ABOUT HERE.
HALFWAY ON THE COMPASS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
WE OUGHT TO BE DOWN
IN ANOTHER TWO HOURS.
HOPE THEY HAVE A HO-JOS.
THERE'S A CITY
JUST AHEAD.
♪♪
WHERE DO WE SET DOWN?
LET'S TAKE HER BACK
IN THOSE HILLS,
WHERE WE CAN FIND A PLACE
TO HIDE THE SHIP.
THEN I'LL FLY OVER THE CITY
IN THE ROCKET SUIT.
OKAY.
YEAH, A GUY IN A LEATHER JACKET
WITH HIS BUTT ON FIRE.
THEY'LL NEVER NOTICE THAT.
[CHUCKLES]
SET HER DOWN
IN THAT CANYON.
SHOULDN'T WE LAND
THE SHIP FIRST?
OKAY.
HEY, THE MOON LOOKS
JUST LIKE ARIZONA, YOU GUYS.
DOES IT REALLY?
- NO.
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
♪♪
HERE, LET ME HELP YOU DOWN.
CUT! EDIT!
ONE SMALL STEP FOR MAN,
ONE GIANT LEAP FOR...
AIYEEE...
MUST GO THROUGH
A LOT OF PANTS.
HEY, IT'S EITHER
ANCIENT GREECE OR VEGAS.
CAESAR'S WORLD.
OH.
WELL, THIS LOOKS TO BE
A WALL.
I'LL GO THIS WAY.
YOU ARE GOING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION, EARTHMAN.
HOW'D THEY KNOW MY NAME?
ENTER THE FIRST DOOR
YOU COME TO.
- IT'S BOB BARKER.
- TURN THE CONTROL.
THE DOOR WILL OPEN.
HMM, HOT, COLD, OPEN.
[DOOR CREAKING]
YOU'D THINK ON THE MOON
THEY'D GET THE CREAKS OUT.
[JOEL, WHISPERING]
GO ON INSIDE, IT'S OKAY.
GO ON.
[WHOOSHING]
EXCUSE ME.
FIRST FLOOR, LINGERIE,
READY-TO-WEAR, NOTIONS, TOUPEES.
- MOON MEN.
- THREE-PEES.
[JOEL CHUCKLES]
I AM ORAKON.
THIS IS MY BROTHER XENON
AND MY OTHER BROTHER XENON.
WELCOME, COMMANDO CODY.
I AM RETTIK,
RULER OF THE MOON.
APPARENTLY, YOU WERE
EXPECTING ME.
OF COURSE.
FOR MANY YEARS
OUR RADIO HAS
KEPT US INFORMED
OF EVENTS ON EARTH.
AND MY MEN THERE
HAVE ADVISED ME
OF YOUR EVERY MOVE.
I'VE LOVED YOU FROM AFAR.
I SEE YOU HAVE ADOPTED
OUR LANGUAGE.
YES, ALL OUR PEOPLE ARE
REQUIRED TO SPEAK ENGLISH
SO WE CAN OPERATE MORE
EFFICIENTLY IN YOUR COUNTRY.
AND WEAR UNDERWEAR
ON OUR HEADS.
MIND TELLING ME WHY YOUR MEN
ARE CARRYING OUT
THAT CAMPAIGN OF DESTRUCTION
ON EARTH?
IT'S AN ELECTION YEAR.
THEY ARE MERELY SOFTENING
UP YOUR DEFENSES
FOR OUR IMPENDING
INVASION.
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO INVADE THE EARTH?
BECAUSE THE ATMOSPHERE
ON THE MOON
HAS BECOME
IS SO THIN AND DRY
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE FOR US
TO RAISE FOOD
EXCEPT IN PRESSURIZED
GREENHOUSES
GET A HUMIDIFIER.
SO WE ARE PLANNING
A MASS MIGRATION
TO YOUR WORLD.
YOU'LL FIND THAT CONQUERING
THE EARTH ISN'T SO SIMPLE.
UNLESS YOU BRING TREATS.
BECAUSE OF OUR
ATOMIC WEAPONS.
ON THE MOON WE HAVE
AN ELEMENT, LUNARIAM,
WHICH IS FAR SUPERIOR
TO URANIUM,
AS A BASE FOR
ATOMIC REACTIONS.
AND WE CAN COMPLETELY
CONTROL THE FORCE
OF THESE REACTIONS,
ENABLING US TO BUILD
ATOMIC WEAPONS
RANGING FROM HUGE
CANNONS TO THESE
SMALL RAY PISTOLS.
WISH WE HAD ONE OF THEM
DOOMSDAY MACHINES.
IT'S VERY CONSIDERATE
OF YOU TO GIVE ME
ALL THIS INFORMATION.
YOU DESERVE SOME REWARD
FOR YOUR LONG JOURNEY,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY I
CANNOT PERMIT YOU
TO RETURN TO EARTH
WITH IT.
- WHAT, LOVELY PARTING GIFTS?
- MAYBE I HAVE SOMETHING
TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
EAT LEAD, SPACE PANSY.
[WHOOSHING]
OH, I THOUGHT THAT
WAS A SMOKE DETECTOR.
SO MUCH FOR THE
EFFECTIVENESS OF
YOUR WEAPONS.
NOW I WILL DEMONSTRATE
ONE OF OURS.
BOREDOM?
[FIRES]
[EXPLOSION]
NOT THE PEPPERMILL.
SEIZE HIM!
YOU COULD SEE THEY'RE
A MORE ADVANCED CIVILIZATION,
THEIR FURNITURE
DOESN'T BREAK.
AH, OH, OKAY.
WELL, IT TIPS OVER
BUT IT DOESN'T BREAK.
WAIT, HOLD STILL, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT.
NO, NOT HIM,
I LOVE HIM.
NOPE.
WHICH ONE?
NO, NOT HIM.
NO, THAT WOULD BE WRONG.
I'VE GOT TO SHOOT
SOMEONE.
[FIRES, EXPLOSION]
OH!
NO!
HE WAS ONE
OF MY FAVORITES.
♪♪
THAT WAS MY ASS FACE.
OH, WE BETTER GET
OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T STAND IT.
WE'RE GETTING TOO
HEAVY FOR THIS.
[FIRES]
[EXPLOSION]
♪♪
WHAT IS THAT NOISE?
WHAT IS THAT, JOEL?
AH, I THINK I KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG.
CAMBOT FOLLOW ME OVER
HERE, LOOK AT THEM,
THEY'RE A BUNCH OF--
SEEM LIKE A BUNCH
OF DEMON DOGS
OR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE DEMON DOGS?
WELL, THEY'RE LIKE CHIHUAHUAS
BUT WITHOUT ANY FLESH.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE COVERING THIS SHIP.
FOLLOW ME BACK.
WE GOT A COUPLE
PROBLEMS, JOE.
WHAT ARE THEY, CROW?
WELL, FIRST, THEY'RE
COVERING THE SHIP,
THEY'RE GOING TO WEIGH
US DOWN, OUR ORBIT'S
GONNA START TO DECAY
AND WE'LL ENTER
EARTH'S ATMOSPHERE.
WE'RE GOING TO BURN UP.
CRISPY CRITTER TIME.
WHAT'S NUMBER TWO?
WELL AS PUPPIES GO
WITH NO FLESH,
THEY GOT LIKE
ZERO CUDDLE FACTOR.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT TO
GET THEM OFF THIS SHIP,
THAT'S ALL THERE IS
TO IT.
I NEED A MAN, A VOLUNTEER
SOMEBODY TO GO OUT THERE
AND SHOO THEM OFF.
OH, I THINK
THE CHOICE IS OBVIOUS.
WHO'S GOT THE MIGHTY
VOICE THAT DOGS
CAN'T SAY NO TO?
- UH, LORNE GREENE.
- YEAH, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT THAT.
I SAID "WHO'S GOT THE
MIGHTY VOICE THAT DOGS CAN'T--"
[BOTH] - YOU DO, TOM SERVO.
- RIGHT, OKAY.
WHO'S WICKED AWESOME?
- UH, THE CLASH.
- EVO.
WHO'S THE HUMAN WHO CAN'T
BREATHE IN SPACE
AND GET DOGS OFF
THEIR SHIP?
RIGHT, I CAN'T, TOM SERVO,
YOU'RE THE MAN.
WHO'S BAD?
- [BOTH] TOM SERVO.
- WHO'S BAD?
- THAT'S RIGHT, I'M BAD.
NOW GIVE ME A ROLLED-UP
NEWSPAPER,
AND DON'T BOTHER
SO SHUT THE DOOR.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
KEEP MY DINNER WARM.
BOY, I'M GLAD HE'S
GOING OUT THERE, JOEL.
I CAN'T EVEN LOOK AT A PLATE
OF SPARE RIBS
WITHOUT GETTING WOOZY.
YEAH, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, CROW,
LET'S JUST WATCH THE MONITOR
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
[TOM]
OKAY, PUPPY PARTY'S OVER.
EVERYBODY OFF, THIS IS TOM
SERVO YOUR WORST
DOGGY NIGHTMARE.
DON'T GET ME MAD,
I DON'T THINK
YOU'D LIKE ME WHEN
I'M MAD.
OH, WAIT, STOP IT.
PUT YOUR LEGS DOWN.
[LAUGHS]
ICKY! CACA!
OH, LET ME IN.
OH, JEEZ, NEXT TIME
I'LL RUB YOUR FACES IN IT.
[BOTH]
OH!
TOM SERVO, WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, JOEL, THERE'S
ONLY ONE WAY TO PUT IT.
THEY DISGRACED THEMSELVES
ON ME.
I FEEL SO DIRTY.
HAVEN'T EFFECTED YOUR
LOOKS ANY.
YUCK, GIVES ME THE WILLIES.
OH WHY WOULD ANYONE WANT
TO DO THAT
TO LOVEABLE OLD ME,
TOM SERVO?
WELL, TOM, LISTEN,
THERE'S BEEN SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN DREADING TELLING YOU
SINCE THE DATE OF
YOUR CREATION.
WHEN YOU WERE STILL
ON THE DRAWING BOARD,
I BASED YOUR PLANS ON
A FIRE HYDRANT.
OH, MAN, YOU CAN LOOK
ME IN THE BUBBLE
AND TELL ME THAT,
I'M A PUBLIC UTILITY.
IT'S OVER, I'M GOING
TO GO HOSE OFF.
[LAUGHS]
♪♪
HOW'D YOU GET RID
OF THOSE DEMON DOGS?
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS THE FEATURE
PRESENTATION.
CASTEÑDA?
I DIDN'T KNOW THIS
WAS GOING TO BE A MUSICAL.
JORGE MONDRAGON, HE MUST
BE PLAYING THE MONSTER.
NO, IT'S THE MUMMY.
"ROBOT."
[ALL]
YAY!
"VS. THE AZTEC MUMMY"?
[ALL]
BOO!
ALFRED SALAZAR.
HE'S A BOXER, ISN'T HE?
I DON'T KNOW.
GARCIA DE LEON.
FOUNTAIN OF YOUTH GUY?
- NO.
- OH.
I DO THINK JOSE LI-HO
IS THE INVENTOR
OF THAT CREAM
SANDWICH THOUGH.
- OH, OKAY.
- THE LI-HO.
WHEN IN MEXICO VISIT
C.L.A.S.A. STUDIOS.
BUT DON'T DRINK THE WATER.
THIS MOVIE IS THE PRODUCER'S
ANSWER TO MONTEZUMA'S REVENGE.
WHEN IN CORAL GABLES, FLORIDA,
VISIT SOUNDLAB INC
AND VISIT OUR
GLASS-BOTTOMED BOATS.
WHEN IN SAN FERNANDO,
VISIT MANUEL.
AND TICKLE HIS BELLY.
TICKLE HIS BELLY.
HE'LL SHAKE HIS LEG
FOR YOU.
NICE TITLE CARD PAINTING,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH, WHAT IS THAT?
KIND OF A MUMMY?
IT LOOKS LIKE
A MUMMY.
MUST'VE TAKEN MINUTES.
MR. MUMMY.
[NARRATOR]
HOW FAR CAN THE HUMAN MIND
PENETRATE THE MYSTERIES
OF THE GREAT BEYOND?
13-FEET, FOUR INCHES,
1920 OLYMPICS.
IS BASED UPON AN
EXTRAORDINARY EXPERIMENT.
CARRIED OUT BY DRS.
HUGHES AND TOONEY--
TOONEY, OH-OH,
FRANCIS, OH.
THERE IS NO DOUBT
AS TO ITS AUTHENTICITY--
EXCEPT FOR OUR
OWN DOUBTS.
PARTICIPATING IN
THE EXPERIMENT
SWORN TO BY A
NOTARY PUBLIC,
PRECLUDE THE POSSIBILITY
OF ANY FRAUD.
THIS PICTURE IS A
COMBINATION OF FACTUAL DATA
MIXED WITH FICTION.
SORT OF LIKE THE
IRAN-CONTRA AFFAIR.
MEXICO, THIS IS THE CITY,
MY NAME IS FRIDAY,
I CARRY A BADGE, I DON'T NEED
NO STINKING BADGE.
THIS IS A REAL CAR,
THE PEOPLE, HOWEVER,
ARE FICTIONAL.
THEIR ACTING,
HOWEVER, IS BAD.
- REAL BAD.
[DOOR CLOSES]
REAL SLOW, TOO.
THESE ARE TWO GUYS
WITH HATS.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
I'M COMING.
JUST A MINUTE.
HOLD ONTO YOUR SHORTS.
I'M COMING.
MY LEGS ARE OLD,
MY TEETH ARE GRAY.
DON'T LEAVE,
I'M COMING.
GOOD EVENING.
- GOOD EVENING.
DR. DIAZ, DR. ESTER, WHAT A
PLEASURE TO HAVE YOU HERE.
DR. KILDARE, DR. SHOAL,
DR. PEPPER.
VERY WELL, THANK YOU,
AND YOU?
THE SAME OLD LABORS,
ALWAYS WORKING.
TRYING TO FIND NEW WAYS
TO HELP PATIENTS
DIE PAINLESSLY.
- FUNNY.
- PLEASE DON'T JOKE,
BUT WON'T YOU COME IN?
MY HUSBAND IS IN THERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
AT HOME THIS EVENING.
IT'S NO TROUBLE, DOCTOR.
WE'RE DELIGHTED.
WHO'D COMPLAIN AT HAVING
THE OPPORTUNITY
OF VISITING WITH SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG LADY
AS YOUR WIFE, FLORA.
FLATTERER.
ISN'T THAT FLOYD,
THE BARBER?
FINE, DOCTOR.
PLEASE, SIT DOWN,
GENTLEMEN.
THANK YOU.
HEY, NOT EVERYBODY SIT
WITH HER,
SPREAD OUT, COME ON.
FLOYD GETS THE
COMFY CHAIR.
I'VE TAKEN THE LIBERTY
OF CALLING YOU HERE
BECAUSE I THINK IT'S TIME
I REVEAL SOMETHING
VERY SERIOUS.
LET'S HEAR IT THEN.
MY UNDERWEAR IS
100 YEARS OLD.
IT'S ABOUT THE AZTEC
BREASTPLATE
AND THE BRACELET,
GENTLEMEN.
HOW IS THAT?
I PUT THEM ON
AT NIGHT AND DANCE.
... THE WHOLE THING WAS
FORGOTTEN LONG AGO.
IT'S A CLOSED BOOK, DOCTOR.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I THOUGHT TOO.
BUT THINGS HAVE HAPPENED
LATELY THAT
I THINK YOU TWO SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT.
MY FRIENDS, BE PATIENT
AND ALLOW ME
TO TELL YOU A STORY.
WE CAN'T.
ALTHOUGH YOU KNOW PART
OF THE HISTORY,
THERE ARE SOME THINGS
YOU IGNORE.
LIKE YOU?
THE BEST THING TO DO IS
TO BEGIN AT THE BEGINNING.
I THINK THAT'S BEGIN
THE BEGIN.
THAT OCCASION YEARS AGO.
FIVE TO BE EXACT,
WHEN WE HELD A CONVENTION
ON PSYCHIATRY IN THE CITY.
I ATTENDED AND GAVE
A TALK ON THE RESULTS
OF MY STUDIES RELATED TO
THE REGRESSION OF A PATIENT
TO A PAST LIFE THROUGH
THE USES OF HYPNOSIS.
MY THEORY WAS GREETED WITH
AMAZEMENT AND INCREDULITY.
I SHOULD'VE OPENED
WITH A JOKE.
AMONG OTHERS ATTENDING
THAT DAY,
- WERE YOU, DR. ESTHER?
- FLOYD, THE BARBER.
AND YOU, DR. VILLAS.
OF COURSE, TENNESSEE
ERNIE FORD.
DR. KRUPP.
AND THE EVIL JUDGE
ROBERT BORK.
SUBJECT OF RIDICULE.
AND I LEFT THE CONVENTION
BITTER AND DEFEATED.
SAME AS ALWAYS.
I GOT TO THE HOUSE FEELING
UNSURE OF THESE IDEAS.
I'D BEEN SQUELCHED.
BUT I JUST COULDN'T ACCEPT
THE OTHER OPINIONS OF MY THEORY
YOU EVER BEEN
SQUELCHED, JOEL?
UH-UH.
THAT NIGHT, FLORA
OFFERED TO UNDERGO
A HYPNOTIC TEST.
SHE BECAME FAUNA,
MY LITTLE HOUSEPLANT.
HEY, IT'S BETSY ROSS,
YOU GUYS.
IN CAMEO.
DURING HER PAST LIFE,
FLORA HAD LIVED AMONG
THE GREAT PEOPLE
OF THE AZTECS.
SHE TOLD OF SUCH
STRANGE THINGS,
AMAZING THINGS.
NAUGHTY THINGS.
HER NAME HAD BEEN XOCHITL.
SHE WAS DEEPLY IN LOVE
WITH A BRAVE
AND HIGH-BORN WARRIOR
CALLED POPOCA.
THEY GOT A MAD
POSH FOR HATS.
SO THEY DECIDED
TO RUN AWAY,
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS
HER SACRED DUTY
TO PRESERVE HER
MAIDENHOOD,
AND BE SACRIFICED TO
THE GOD DE CAPLA COPA.
- THE GOD OF DECAFFEINATED
COFFEE.
- THEY WERE DISCOVERED
BY THE TRIBAL PRIESTS.
THEY PREPARED HEARTY
SOUPS AND BROTHS
AND FORCED THEM
ON THEIR GUESTS
FOR THEY TRULY KNEW
HOW TO HANDLE A HUNGRY MAN.
THIS IS CHICKEN NOODLE SOUP
THAT I LET STEEP
ALL DAY IN THE SUN,
IT'S LIKE SUN TEA.
- BETTER THAN BORSCHT,
- YEP.
FOR YOUR GOOD HEALTH.
SEE, MOMMY'S DRINKING IT,
HMM, NUM-NUM-NUM-NUM-NUM,
OPEN UP, HERE'S
THE STEAM SHOVEL,
HOT, HOT.
NOTHING LIKE
A HOT STEAM SHOVEL.
GETS YOU GOING
IN THE MORNING.
[ALMADA]
AS PUNISHMENT, THE WARRIOR
WAS BURIED ALIVE,
AND AN ETERNAL CURSE
WAS PLACED UPON HIM.
THEN THINGS GOT BAD.
GHEORGHE ZAMFIR, MASTER
OF THE PAN FLUTE, PLAYED.
BUT IT DIDN'T LAST LONG.
AS PART OF HER PUNISHMENT,
SHE WAS SUBMITTED TO
THE DREADED BINOCULAR JOKE.
[SINGING IN AZTEC]
THEN, ETHEL MERMAN OPENED
WITH A SONG.
OH, THIS IS HORRIBLE.
[VOLUME DECREASES]
[MAKING CHANTING NOISES]
KIND OF LIKE FINGERS
ON A CHALKBOARD.
[SINGING CONTINUES]
- WHAT THE?
- THAT'S BETTER.
[MUSIC DECREASES IN VOLUME]
PEELING THE CHROME
OFF MY BODY.
[DECREASES IN VOLUME AGAIN]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SINGING]
♪ MAZOLA CORN GOODNESS ♪
- [HUMMING]
- HEY, IT'S A PERUVIAN
ALLSTATE REPRESENTATIVE.
HE'S STONED.
[JOEL LAUGHS]
THE CEREMONY LASTED
WELL INTO THE NIGHT.
WHAT A PARTY.
I'VE GOT RHYTHM
IN MY DIODES.
LET'S SEE, NOW, WHAT CAN
WE DO WITH HER HAIR?
WELL, WE COULD GIVE HER
A SWINGING BOB,
OR, OH, SHE'S SCHEDULED
TO DIE,
JUST GIVE HER A BLOW DRY
AND A RINSE.
IT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR
THAT THEY TEASE HER HAIR
RIGHT BEFORE SHE'S KILLED.
TEASING'S ALWAYS BAD.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
ONE OF THE MOST BORING RIDES
AT DISNEYLAND, DO YOU
REALIZE THAT, YOU GUYS?
AZTECS OF THE CARIBBEAN?
HOW LOW WILL SHE GO?
THEN SHE WAS
BENT AT THE WAIST?
HEY, WATCH YOUR
HAND, BUDDY.
KIND OF LOOKS LIKE
DIRTY DANCING, DOESN'T IT?
[SINGING]
♪ I'VE REACHED THE END ♪
♪ OF MY LIFE ♪
♪ AND I'M WAITING
FOR THE KNIFE TO FALL ♪
MAN, LOOK, IT'S THE JETS.
[SPEAKING IN AZTEC]
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
HE'S SAYING LIVE FAST,
DIE YOUNG,
AND LEAVE A GOOD-LOOKING
CORPSE.
THAT WAS YEARS BEFORE
JAMES DEAN
EVEN EXISTED.
[ALMADA]
SHE WAS ADORNED WITH THE
BRACELETS AND
THE BREASTPLATE,
WHICH WERE ENGRAVED
WITH HIEROGLYPHICS,
INDICATING WHERE THE AZTEC
TREASURE WAS HIDDEN.
THEN THEY CUT OUT
HER HEART.
BUT AS SHE BEGAN TO
REGAIN CONSCIOUSNESS,
AND THE EXACT MOMENT I
CAME TO THE END
OF MY LITTLE EXPERIMENT,
SHE STRUGGLED
AND BEGAN TO SHOUT.
[SCREAMING]
FLORA HAD A TERRIBLE
ATTACK OF SOME KIND,
AND HER BLOOD PRESSURE
DROPPED TO SUCH
AN EXTENT, THAT WE
WERE AFRAID SHE MIGHT DIE.
A COUPLE OF WEEKS LATER,
WE DISCOVERED THAT
DR. KRUPP,
A MAN WHO HAD SUDDENLY BECOME
A DANGEROUS CRIMINAL
IN THE UNDERWORLD,
HAD BEEN THERE SPYING
DURING MY EXPERIMENT.
♪♪
[ALMADA]
THE EXPERIMENT HAD BEEN
A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
BUT SINCE WE REALIZED THAT
NO ONE WOULD BELIEVE US
UNLESS WE COULD COME UP
WITH ABSOLUTE PROOF.
WE DECIDED TO SEARCH
IN THE BASEMENT.
I COULDN'T WAIT TO SHOW
THEM MY BUMPER POOL TABLE.
AND MY FINE SELECTION
OF JAMS AND JELLIES
AND A COMPOST THAT I HAD
LAID OUT.
♪♪
FLORA, OUR GUIDE, WAS TIED
TO MY WAIST
SO WE WOULDN'T
BE SEPARATED.
♪♪
WHY FLOYD BROUGHT
THE BEAVER, I DON'T KNOW.
OH, MY, THERE'S A LIGHT.
WE'RE THINKING OF
EXPANDING THIS WHOLE THING.
MAKING A RUMPUS ROOM.
FOR OUR RUMPUS.
AND SPEAKING OF RUMPUSES,
THERE'S FLORA.
LEFT FOOT, RIGHT,
LEFT RIGHT.
AH!
WE'LL HAVE THIS BLOCKING
DOWN IN NO TIME.
SUDDENLY, THERE IT WAS,
MY SIX-SIDED BUMPER
POOL TABLE.
I THINK A SWAG LAMP HERE
AND A BEADED CURTAIN
WOULD REALLY BRIGHTEN
THE PLACE UP.
♪ ONCE A JOLLY SWAG LAMP ♪
♪ WAITED BY THE BOULEVARD ♪
♪♪
[WHISPERING]
GO THAT WAY.
THERE WAS
NO DENYING IT,
WE WERE WALKING
IN A CIRCLE.
♪♪
PROFESSOR, I THINK WE'RE UP
AGAINST A DEAD END.
IT CAN'T BE POSSIBLE.
THE AZTECS WOULDN'T BUILD
A SECRET PASSAGE WAY
JUST TO HAVE IT END UP
FOR NO RHYME OR REASON.
NOT THE KIND OF AZTEC
YOU'RE USED TO DEALING WITH.
IT'S A CUL DE SAC.
PROFESSOR, IT
SOUNDS HOLLOW.
WELL, STOP KNOCKING
ON MY HEAD.
BUT IT'S SO THICK
THAT IT'S SENSELESS
TO TRY TO BREAK THROUGH.
MY HEAD?
OR THE WALL?
I'LL PUSH.
PINACATE, LEND ME
A HAND, PLEASE.
NOT THAT HAND,
YOUR CLEAN HAND.
OH, THAT WAS
HELP IF YOU'RE CLEAN.
FLORA, COME ON.
WE JARRED IT OPEN.
GO AHEAD, BEAVE.
IT'S THE SAME SET
WE WERE ON BEFORE.
IT'S THE PHANTOM
OF THE OPERA.
- OUCH!
- THIS MUST BE THE ROOM
BENEATH THE PYRAMID.
- GOOD
- YES, BUT I KNOW IT ISN'T
THE TEMPLE.
- LOOK WHAT I FOUND,
COME HERE.
- A LAUNDRY CHUTE.
WHAT IS IT?
IT LOOKS LIKE A WELL.
WELL, I THINK IT'S
AN AIR SHAFT,
BUT UNDOUBTEDLY
IT WILL LEAD US SOMEWHERE.
PROBABLY TO THE TEMPLE.
MAYBE THE AIR.
WELL, THEN, WHAT
ARE WE WAITING FOR?
NO DOUBT IT WILL
ADVANCE THE PLOT.
- COME ON.
- THIN AS IT IS.
WOMEN, CHILDREN FIRST,
I'LL STAND HERE
AND HOLD THE FLASHLIGHT.
REMARKABLE, IT WAS
THE NEIGHBOR'S BASEMENT.
ONCE AGAIN, I CAN USE
THEIR VHS
WITHOUT THEM KNOWING.
WE SHOVED EVERYBODY
THROUGH THE LITTLE HOLE.
[ALMADA]
AFTER DESCENDING SEVERAL
FLIGHTS OF STAIRS,
WE SUDDENLY ENCOUNTERED
THE HAIR-RAISING FACE
OF THE GOD DE CAPLA COPA.
WE HAD REACHED
THE LOWER TEMPLE,
AND THE AZTEC TOMB
THAT FLORA HAD MENTIONED.
AND THE LIGHTING
WAS GOOD.
YOU COULD SHOOT
A SCENE HERE.
♪♪
LIGHTS, PLEASE.
THERE WE CAME ACROSS
THE SKELETON
OF WHAT HAD ONCE
BEEN XOCHITL.
- LOOKS LIKE CHICKEN WINGS.
- SOLID GOLD BREASTPLATE.
XOCHITL.
THIS IS HORRIBLE
TO THINK
I WAS SHE.
BUT YOU'RE YOU NOW.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE THE FIRST
PERSONS TO BREAK IN HERE.
THE OTHER PEOPLE
USED THE DOOR.
IT'S A WORLD THAT
SLUMBERED ALL THESE YEARS.
AND BEGINS TO
AWAKEN NOW.
WE FOUND WHAT
WE WANTED SO BADLY.
THE SUMP PUMP.
NO, EDWARD.
DON'T DO IT.
[ALL]
DO IT, EDWARD, DO IT!
♪♪
THERE'S A TOOTSIE POP
STILL IN HIS MOUTH.
- IT'S KOJAK.
- IT REALLY LASTS A LONG TIME.
THE HEAD SHOULD
REALLY SCREW RIGHT OFF.
THIS'LL LOOK SWELL
IN MY OFFICE.
NOW AT LAST I'LL BE ABLE
TO DEMONSTRATE THIS
TO MY COLLEAGUES.
AND PROVE MY THEORY.
IT'S SIMPLY AMAZING.
SIMPLY.
JUST A FEUD AFTER I GOT
THE BREASTPLATE,
I ASKED YOU ALL HERE,
INCLUDING DR. KRUPP
- AS YOU'LL RECALL.
- CERTAINLY.
I'D SAY THAT IT WAS
THE GREATEST EXPERIENCE
- OF MY LIFE.
- AND MINE, TOO.
ME, TOO.
- YOU MUST ALSO RECALL THAT I
-- I'LL BUY INTO THAT.
SAID THAT I'D STUDIED
THE BREASTPLATE AND THAT I
- TRIED TO DECIPHER THE
HIEROGLYPHICS
- SVELDT
AND SEE WHAT THEY MEANT.
SINCE I KNEW THAT THE MESSAGE
WOULD TELL HOW TO FIND
- THAT HIDDEN TREASURE.
- YES, BUT I REMEMBER
YOUR TELLING THAT YOU
ALSO NEEDED THE BRACELET.
EXACTLY, DOCTOR.
ONE OBJECT COMPLIMENTED
THE OTHER.
- THEY'RE AN ENSEMBLE.
- WITHOUT THE BRACELET,
IT WAS SIMPLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO DECIPHER THE CODE.
SO I DECIDED TO GO
BACK FOR IT,
IN SPITE OF THE AZTEC CURSE
THAT SURROUNDED IT.
HE WHO DEFILES A TOMB
OF THE AZTECS,
AND FINDS THE SACRED PLATE,
WILL RUN THE RISK
OF DEATH, AND HIS FAMILY
AS WELL, UNTIL THE
BREASTPLATE IS REPLACED.
- AND GET BIG BUCK TEETH.
- WHAT IS HE, ROD MCKUEN?
LIGHTS.
SO ONCE AGAIN
THE THREE OF US
GOT TOGETHER AND
RETURNED TO THE TOMB.
THIS TIME LOADED
OUT OF OUR MINDS.
WHEN WE REACHED THERE
AND I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO PICK UP THE BRACELET,
MY FATHER-IN-LAW
STUMBLED ON SOMETHING
AND CALLED MY ATTENTION
TO IT.
- OW.
- LOOK HERE.
I STUMBLED ON SOMETHING.
IT'S MY FOOT.
IT'S ATTACHED TO
THE BOTTOM OF MY ANKLE.
BOY, WERE WE DRUNK.
IT'S AN AZTEC IUD.
LOOK THERE, DOESN'T THAT
GRAVE BELONG TO POPOCA?
YES, ACCORDING TO
THE LEGEND, IT DOES.
IN THAT CASE, WHERE
IS HE NOW?
[SHUFFLING]
IT WAS SCATMAN CROTHERS.
[SHUFFLING CONTINUES]
HEY, THIS ONE SAYS
"FLUSH TWICE
THE CAFETERIA'S
A LONG WAY OFF."
WHOA, WHAT'S THAT?
GUARD!
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
WE WERE THE FIRST ONES HERE.
HEY, ZIP 'EM UP, MAN,
SOMEONE'S COMING.
[ZIPPING SOUND]
♪ ME AND MY SHADOW ♪
AND THEN OUT OF THE DARKNESS,
APPEARED THE GHASTLY
AND TERRIFYING POPOCA.
THE AZTEC WARRIOR
HAD COME BACK TO LIFE.
COME BACK TO
LIFE TO RETRIEVE
THE OBJECTS THAT HAD BEEN
LEFT IN HIS CARE
FOR ETERNITY.
[SQUEALING NOISES]
PARROT BOY.
ICE, I'M MELTING MAN TO MAN.
[SNIFFLING]
MUMMY, AZTEC MUMMY.
[GROANING]
TURN THEM OFF AGAIN.
LIGHTS AGAIN.
[GROANS]
IT'S A FLOOR SHORE.
IT'S A LOVELY SINGING VOICE.
THIS GUY'S GOT A BIG
CAREER IN SHOWBIZ.
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
THAT REALLY HURT.
NOW JUGGLING'S NOT
IN HIS ROUTINE.
[MOANS]
- AH...
- PINACATE.
GUYS, HELP ME, HE'S
GIVING ME A SNUGGY.
HELP ME.
PULL, PULL ME, FAST.
[ALL GROANING]
[STRUGGLING NOISES]
THE TRIPLE WEDGEE
FROM A MUMMY.
- LIGHTS.
- TO BE PERFECTLY FRANK,
I THOUGHT MY TIME HAD COME.
IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR
MY FRIENDS,
I'D BEEN TORN TO PIECES.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
A MUMMY COMES BACK TO LIFE
AFTER HUNDREDS OF YEARS
IN A SUB BUNKER.
DR. DIAZ, YOU HAVE MY
WORD OF HONOR
THAT THE STORY I HAVE
BEEN TELLING IS THE TRUTH.
OKAY, MIXED WITH
A LITTLE FICTION.
OKAY, I'M LYING
MY BUTT OFF.
BECAUSE HE LOVED
YOUNG XOCHITL.
HIS CURSE WAS TO GUARD THE
PRICELESS BRACELET
AS WELL AS
THE GOLDEN BREASTPLATE.
TO DO SO FOR ALL ETERNITY.
OR A 100,000 MILES,
WHATEVER CAME FIRST.
HIS POOR SOUL WOULD
NEVER FIND REPOSE.
CONTINUE, EDWARD.
- WELL THE BAT ON MANY--
- DON'T PICK ME UP ON IT.
[GROANS]
LET'S GO, CROW.
- YOU NEED TO MOP IN HERE.
- RIGHT.
I THOUGHT THE WHOLE BUSINESS
HAD BEEN FORGOTTEN.
BUT I FOUND THAT
THE AZTEC CURSE
STILL FOLLOWED US.
ONE NIGHT, THE MUMMY CAME
TO THIS HOUSE
TO GET HIS TREASURE PIECES.
AND HE KIDNAPPED FLORA.
♪♪
OH, MAN, I DON'T THINK
I CAN HANDLE THE SOUND
OF THOSE DOGS
BARKING ANYMORE.
AT LEAST THE
THE THEATER'S SOUNDPROOF.
TOO BAD, THEY MIGHT DROWN
OUT THE SOUND
OF THAT BIG DOG
ON THE FILM.
[KNOCKING SOUNDS]
WHAT IS IT, TOM SERVO?
I THINK, YEAH, JOEL,
I THINK ONE OF THOSE
DEMON DOGS IS DOING
"A SHAVE AND A HAIRCUT"
KNOCK ON THE BACK DOOR.
WHAT?
WHAT IS IT, FELLA?
[WHIMPERING]
I THINK HE'S TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING.
[WHIMPERING]
DAD? HE'S TRAPPED?
UNDER A ROCK?
DOWN IN DEAD ROCK CANYON?
[MAN]
STOP PATRONIZING ME
AND OPEN THIS DOOR.
DON'T LET HIM IN.
HEY, COME ON IN HERE.
UP, UP, COME ON UP.
UH-OH, NOT ON THE FURNITURE,
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
I AM ENOCH, KING
AND CHARISMATIC LEADER
OF THE DOG PEOPLE,
- ARF-ARF.
- CUTE.
WE HAVE TRAVELLED
MANY PARTS
AS TO PRAY TO
THE GIANT BONE
AND JUST MAYBE
GET A TASTE.
GIANT DOG BONE?
YES, BUT WE DID NOT
KNOW THE BONE
WOULD BE INHABITED.
HM.
JOEL, I THINK THE BONE
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
IS OUR SHIP.
HEY, CAMBOT, PUT
THE SCHEMATIC DRAWING
OF THE SATELLITE LOVE,
THE 25-25, UP ON SCREEN,
I THINK IT'S UNDER
25-25 IN YOUR FILE.
[JOEL]
WOW, IT LOOKS EXACTLY
LIKE A GIANT DOG BONE.
NOT JUST ANY BONE,
BUT THE SACRED NYLON
CHEW TOY
WRITTEN OF BY THE
HOLY RUG WEATHER RAT,
RUG WEATHERMAN,
JOHN AMBRY.
OUR INTENTION WAS
TO BURY YOU ON
THE FAR SIDE OF THE MOON.
BUT NOW WE'LL HAVE TO
CHANGE OUR PLANS.
WOW, WELL, LISTEN
YOU GOT TO GET
YOUR FOLLOWERS OFF
OUR SHIP,
THERE'S SO MANY OF THEM
AND THEY'RE MULTIPLYING
AT SUCH AN
ALARMING RATE,
THAT WE'RE GOING
TO GO INTO
THE EARTH'S ATMOSPHERE
AND EXPLODE.
YEAH, AND THEN
YOU'LL BE HOT DOGS.
[BOTH GROWL]
HEY, COME ON, CROW,
- COME ON, HE'S OUR GUEST--
- NOT GOING TO BE A PROBLEM,
AT MY SIGNAL,
THE DOGS WILL LEAVE.
BUT THEY OBEY ME,
AND ONLY ME.
FIRST, LET US
EXCHANGE PLEASANTRIES.
THEN, WE WILL
DRINK TRANIA.
FROM A DISH ON
THE FLOOR, BOY?
- [BOTH GROWL]
- CROW, NOW STOP IT, LISTEN.
HE HASN'T EVEN MET
EVERYBODY,
WELL, EXCEPT FOR
TOM SERVO, RIGHT?
AH, THE ATTRACTIVE ONE.
HEY, WATCH IT, PAL,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT
100% PRIME CUT AMERICAN
ROBOTIC MALE.
AND I DON'T PARTY
WITH PUPPIES,
- I'M OUT OF HERE.
- OH.
WELL, MY NAME IS JOEL,
AND I'M FROM
THE PLANET EARTH.
WHERE I COME FROM,
DOGS ARE MAN'S BEST FRIEND.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
YEAH, IT'S TRUE.
AND YOU MET CROW
OVER HERE.
SHAKE, BOY, SHAKE.
- I DON'T LIKE THIS BIRD--
- HEY, SIT.
BUT NOW I'LL EXPLAIN
HOW TO RID YOUR SHIP
OF THE DOGS.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE,
YOU HAVEN'T MET GYPSY YET.
- THIS IS GYPSY.
- AH, AH, AH.
HEY, GYPSY, NO.
GYPSY, NO.
[GROWLING]
- COME ON, OH.
- HEY.
- OH, NO, WE'RE KIBBLE.
- WAY TO GO, GIRL.
[ALARM BUZZING]
MOVIE SIGN!
BACK ON.
- [ALMADA] HE TIED HER TO THE
SACRIFICIAL STONE,
- NOW, LET'S GO HOME.
♪ TIE A SLEEPING FLORA ♪
♪ ROUND THE ALTAR STONE ♪
- HEY.
- OBVIOUSLY, THE MUMMY INTENDED
TO MAKE HISTORY REPEAT ITSELF.
HE WAS GOING TO CUT OUT
FLORA'S HEART AND OFFER
IT TO THE GOD DE CAPLA COPA.
THE THREE OF US RUSHED
TO THE PYRAMID
TO TRY TO RESCUE FLORA.
AND WE STOOD TRANSFIXED
FOR A MOMENT
AT THE SCENE WE SAW.
THE MUMMY WAS STANDING
NEXT TO THE STONE.
HE WAS HOLDING A KNIFE
HIGH IN HIS RIGHT HAND.
I JUMPED TO THE FLOOR
AND LUCKILY WAS ABLE
TO HIT THE BLADE
WITH A BULLET.
DUH.
[ALMADA]
IT LUNGED AT ME AND
IT'S ENORMOUS HANDS
GOT HOLD OF MY THROAT.
LIFE WAS LEAVING ME
RAPIDLY WHEN FLORA'S
FATHER SUDDENLY HELD A CROSS
UP IN FRONT OF ITS FACE.
WHICH WAS ODD BECAUSE
HE WAS JEWISH.
... HOLD THE MUMMY AT BAY
WHILE WE FREED FLORA.
IN A FRENZY, WE UNTIED HER
AND GOT HER AWAY
FROM THE STONE.
THEN THE PROFESSOR ORDERED
US TO GET HER
OUT OF THE PYRAMID.
GET OUT OF THE PYRAMID.
HIS TONE WAS SO ADAMANT,
AND I WAS SO CONCERNED
FOR FLORA'S SAFETY
THAT WE OBEYED HIM BLINDLY.
AND WHEN WE GOT OUT,
I REALIZED THAT HE
HADN'T FOLLOWED US.
FLOYD'S OUT, THANK GOD.
OH, WHAT ABOUT OPIE.
IN THAT VERY INSTANT,
- A TREMENDOUS EXPLOSION.
- OOP, YES.
OH, EXPLOSION, YES.
♪♪
THE PROFESSOR HAD GIVEN
UP HIS LIFE
IN ORDER TO SAVE OURS.
AND HIS CAREER.
MUMMY HAD STAYED UNDER
TONS OF BOULDERS,
AND THE BAT HAD BEEN
SENT TO PRISON,
- THE BAT?
- OF COURSE WE THOUGHT
THE WHOLE BUSINESS
HAD COME TO AN END.
- BUT IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
THAT WAY
- WHO'S THE BAT?
THE BAT, WHO IS REALLY
THE INFAMOUS DR. KRUPP.
[ALL]
OH.
IN HIS MAD DETERMINATION
TO GET MY TREASURE,
HE KIDNAPPED MY DAUGHTER,
AND FLORA AND THEN
HYPNOTIZED HER.
DO TELL US THE REST,
MY FRIEND.
THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
IN THIS STATE, SHE TOOK
THE DOCTOR TO THE AZTEC TOMB.
HE IMMEDIATELY LOCATED
THE MUMMY,
TAKING THE BREASTPLATE
AND THE BRACELET.
WELL, KRUPP CALLED ME ON THE
PHONE NOT TOO MUCH LATER.
I WAS ORDERED TO GO THERE
AND DECIPHER THE HIEROGLYPHICS,
TO ENABLE THE DEMON
TO LOCATE THE TREASURE.
AND YOU AGREED?
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT I
HAD TO OBEY?
TO SAVE MY WIFE WHO
HAD BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY THE DOCTOR.
- AND MY LITTLE GIRL--
- AH, BUT THERE'S ANOTHER
THING YOU SHOULD KNOW.
HE NEEDED THE AZTEC TREASURE
FOR A SPOT ON HIS WALL
IN THE REC ROOM.
HE NEEDED THAT AZTEC
TREASURE TO WORK ON
AN EXPERIMENT.
HE ALSO SAID THE EXPERIMENT,
OF COURSE, WAS COSTLY.
NOW YOU KNOW HOW
I WAS FORCED TO DO IT.
I WENT TO KRUPP'S LABORATORY.
AND BEGAN TO DECIPHER
THE HIEROGLYPHICS.
TENS OF THOSE
CRIMINALS
LIVES WERE IN GRAVE DANGER.
OUR ONLY HOPE WAS
THE MUMMY,
GUIDED BY UNKNOWN FORCES,
WOULD BE ABLE TO FIND
DR. KRUPP'S HIDEOUT
JUST THE WAY HE HAD
FOUND MY HOUSE
ON A PREVIOUS OCCASION.
HE COULD CALL INFORMATION.
BUT THE MOMENT ARRIVED
WHEN I COULD STALL NO LONGER.
I FINISHED IT.
THAT'S FINE.
LET'S SEE HERE, "WE
THE PEOPLE OF..."
HEY, THIS'LL
NEVER WORK.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO
NOW, DON'T YOU BRUNO?
START A VICTORY GARDEN?
HAVE A BAKE SALE?
SUPPORT RADIO FREE EUROPE?
COLLECT SHINY THINGS?
BUY BONDS WHERE YOU
WORK OR BANK?
GET A GUN?
GET A GUN, THAT'S
A GOOD THING.
HE ALWAYS RESORTS
TO VIOLENCE.
JUST WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO, MURDER US?
NO, I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
YOU UNSCRUPULOUS PIG.
MUMMY'S HOME.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT.
[GUNFIRE]
BULLETS BOUNCE RIGHT OFF.
OR GO RIGHT THROUGH.
DOESN'T REALLY HAVE IT.
YEAH, KEEP SHOOTING, BRUNO,
IT'S GOING TO WORK, REALLY.
AH!
- BEAUTIFUL.
- [SCREAMS]
OOPS.
RIGHT WHERE IT HURTS.
ON THE FLOOR.
[SCREAMS]
HE'S WEARING A
SMOKING JACKET, YOU GUYS.
I'M OUT.
- WHOA.
- THERE'S SOME FURNITURE
WE MISSED.
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
I'VE SAVED THE BEAVER.
I'VE SAVED FLORA.
LOOK OUT.
C'MON, BEAVE, LET'S
GO CHECK THIS OUT.
THEY SEEM STUNNED.
NO!
DOCTOR, HELP ME!
CAN'T YOU HEAR?
NO... HELP ME!
YEAH, YOU'RE FIRST ON THE LIST
OF PEOPLE TO HELP.
PLEASE, HELP ME!
HELP ME!
[ALMADA]
THE MUMMY REALIZED
WHO THE CRIMINALS WERE
AND SETTLED ACCOUNTS WITH THEM.
THEN, WHEN HE SAW
THE DOCTOR TRYING TO ESCAPE,
HE PICKED HIM UP
LIKE A RAG DOLL
AND THREW HIM INTO
A PIT FULL OF RATTLERS.
EVERY GOOD LABORATORY HAS
AAH!
- WOULD THAT BE A BAD TOUCH?
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
WE WERE TIRED, BUT IT WAS
A GOOD KIND OF TIRED.
MUMMY'S DONE CLEANING.
[ALMADA]
AFTERWARDS, WITH THE BREASTPLATE
AND THE BRACELET
IN HIS HAND,
HE SLOWLY SHUFFLED AWAY
INTO THE DARKNESS
AND SOON WAS LOST FROM SIGHT.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
THE STRONG AFFECTION
I HAD FOR FLORA'S FATHER.
SUCH A KIND MAN
WHOSE INTELLIGENT ADVICE
BROUGHT ABOUT OUR SALVATION.
AND THE MUMMY WENT
BACK TO THE PYRAMID?
NO, HE HAD TWO NIGHTS
AT THE COPA.
NO, THEY DESTROYED
HIS TEMPLE.
HE HAD NO REASON
TO GO THERE.
IN THAT CASE, CAN'T YOU TELL US
WHERE HE IS?
- PERMIT ME TO CONTINUE.
- HEY, IT'S YOUR MOVIE.
ALL THESE TRAGIC HAPPENINGS
COULDN'T GO UNATTENDED,
SO I WENT TO THE POLICE.
THEN I RETURNED
TO KRUPP'S HIDEOUT,
ACCOMPANIED BY THE CHIEF
OF POLICE,
AND A COUPLE OF HIS MEN.
YOU CAN IMAGINE OUR SURPRISE
WHEN WE DISCOVERED
THE PLACE WAS COMPLETELY EMPTY.
EXCEPT FOR ALL
THIS GARBAGE.
THE LABORATORY HAD BEEN
DISMANTLED,
AND THE BODIES
OF THE CRIMINALS
THAT THE MUMMY HAD KILLED
HAD ALSO DISAPPEARED.
THEY WERE DISMANTLED AS WELL.
CONTINUING OUR SEARCH,
WE HURRIED TO THE SNAKE PIT.
I WAS AWESTRUCK
WHEN I REALIZED
THE THE BODY OF DR. KRUPP
WAS NO LONGER DOWN THERE.
- AW...
- THEN, TO OUR HORROR,
WE DISCOVERED THAT THERE WAS
A SMALL DOOR
IN THE BACK WALL OF THE PIT,
THROUGH WHICH
THE DOCTOR COULD
HAVE ESCAPED.
HE WAS SUCH A LARGE MAN,
HOW COULD HE?
OBVIOUSLY, THE DOCTOR
HAD ESCAPED.
AND STRANGELY, I DON'T THINK
HE'D BEEN BITTEN.
THE MAN'S RUNNING LOOSE.
SO THAT WOULD MEAN THAT
THE DOCTOR KEPT TRYING
TO COME BY THOSE ARTICLES
SO THAT HE COULD LOCATE
THE TREASURE.
YOU'RE RIGHT, MY FRIEND,
HE DID JUST THAT.
HE BEGAN TO BOTHER US
A COUPLE OF WEEKS LATER.
IT HAPPENED QUITE SUDDENLY,
YOU SEE.
ONE DARK NIGHT...
THIS IS THE HOUSE.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THIS PLAN OF YOURS
IS GONNA WORK, DOC?
YOU'LL SEE.
NOW I WANT YOU TO BE QUIET.
KEEP STILL, AND DON'T MAKE
THE SLIGHTEST NOISE.
PEAS AND CARROTS,
PEAS AND CARROTS...
I WISH THAT YOU COME
TO MY SIDE.
♪♪
FLORA, I COMMAND YOU
TO COME TO ME.
I THINK HE'S USING
TELEFLORA.
FLORA, I COMMAND YOU
TO COME TO ME.
USE THE DOORBELL.
DOORKNOB.
FLORA, ARE YOU LISTENING?
COME HERE TO ME.
IS HE SPEAKING INTO
HIS GLOVE?
MUST BE A PARTY LINE.
976-FLORA?
- STAND UP.
- WEAR SOMETHING SHEER.
PUT ON A HOUSECOAT.
FLORA, DO NOT TRY
TO FIGHT IT, COME HERE.
NOTICE YOU NEVER ACTUALLY
SEE HER GET DRESSED.
NOW, OPEN THE DOOR THIS TIME.
DON'T WALK THROUGH IT.
- GOOD GIRL.
- WELL DONE.
THAT'LL SAVE
SOME REPAIR
HEY, CLOSE IT ALL THE WAY.
WERE YOU BORN IN A BARN?
FLORA, DO NOT TRY
TO FIGHT IT, COME HERE!
STEP, STEP, STEP, KICK.
STEP, KICK.
RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT.
OKAY, IT'S ALL FLAT
FROM HERE, FLORA.
OH.
- SHE'S NOT FALLING FOR IT.
- NO.
SHE'S NO PUSHOVER
LOUD CLOCK...
AND KETTLE DRUM.
FLORA, ARE YOU LISTENING?
I COMMAND YOU TO COME TO ME.
I'M COMING, I'M COMING.
FLORA, YOU ARE TO DO
AS I COMMAND-- COME HERE.
DIGGING FOR GOLD,
BRUNO?
OKAY, BRUNO, WHEN SHE
PASSES IN FRONT OF THE CAR,
HONK REALLY LOUD.
[IMITATING CAR HORN HONKING]
LOVE ME AND MY
DEFORMED FRIEND.
YOU CAN HEAR THE WAVES
THAT ARE BEING SENT OUT
BY THAT MUMMY, CAN YOU NOT?
AND THE GUY IN THE CAR.
I KNOW WELL THAT YOU ARE ABLE
TO LEAD US TO HIM
YES, I CAN.
THEN TELL US,
WHERE IS POPOCA?
THE BEER BARREL POPOCA?
IN THE ANCIENT CEMETERY.
COME WITH ME.
IS THE ANCIENT CEMETERY
DENOMINATIONAL?
MEANWHILE, IN THE ANCIENT
CEMETERY,
THEY WERE LOOKING
FOR THE MUMMY.
BUT FIRST, LET'S KICK OVER
SOME GRAVE STONES, HEE HEE HEE.
YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD MAKE
ANOTHER EXCELLENT
MINIATURE GOLF COURSE,
LIKE THE OTHER MOVIE.
EACH HOLE WOULD BE DEADLY.
[CHUCKLES]
THAT LAST STEP IS A DOOZY.
LOW OVERHEAD.
BUT GRAVE CONSEQUENCES.
- YIKES.
- SORRY.
- I'LL SHUT YOU OFF.
- DON'T DO IT.
- COME ON, BRUNO, KEEP UP.
AND STOP PICKING YOUR NOSE.
LOOK, PETER GRAVES!
[LAUGHS]
WHO'S BURIED
IN PETER'S GRAVE?
JAMES ARNESS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ANSWER ME!
WE'RE HITTING PEOPLE.
COME NOW, FLORA.
MUST HAVE BEEN
A DISPOSABLE CHARACTER.
COME ON, WE MUST HURRY.
SHUFFLE, SHUFFLE.
STEP, STEP, STEP.
NO NEED TO HURRY,
THE PLOT WILL SUPPORT
ALL OF THIS
FRIKKIN' SLOWNESS.
[ALL)
LIONS AND TIGERS AND BEARS,
OH, MY.
SEE, THIS'LL BE
OUR NEW HOME.
YOU SEE, THERE'LL BE YOU
AND ME, AND BRUNO MAKES THREE.
AND MY LITTLE
DEFORMED FRIEND.
- IS THIS THE PLACE?
- YES.
KNOCK TWICE.
TELL 'EM SAM SENT YOU.
[CHAIN RATTLES]
SHH!
YOU TRYING TO WAKE THE DEAD?
IT'S OPEN.
AT LEAST CARRY HER
ACROSS THE THRESHOLD.
SURE AM GLAD FLORA WORE
HER PHOSPHORESCENT DRESS.
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT'S
THE CURSE OF THE MUMMY, CROW?
- CURSE OF THE MUMMY?
- YEAH.
IT'S BEING-- NOT BEING ABLE
TO DRESS WHEN YOU ROB A GRAVE.
I HATE THAT.
I'VE HAD THIS DREAM BEFORE.
I'M IN MY PAJAMAS,
I'M IN A CRYPT...
I'M BEING CHASED
BY A BIG BANANA.
OH, MAN, HIS FACE LOOKS LIKE
COTTAGE CHEESE.
IT LOOKS LIKE A DIET PLATE.
YOU DEVIL.
YOU STINKING DEVIL!
HOW I'D LIKE TO CHOP
YOUR ROTTEN FLESH TO PIECES!
BRUNO, STOP LETTING HATE
RUN YOUR LIFE.
IT WOULD CERTAINLY
BE GREAT TO DO SO...
WHO'S HE HIDING
HIS FACE FROM?
HIS AGENT, I THINK.
HE'S GOING TO MAKE
MY EXPERIMENT,
SO WE MUST WAIT.
WAIT?
WHEN I GOT SO MUCH HATE
EATING DOWN DEEP INSIDE
OF MY GUTS?
YOU AIN'T GOT NO IDEA
WHAT IT IS TO LIVE LIKE THIS!
OH, MAN, LOOK, THEY TAPED
PLASTIC GOOP TO HIS FACE.
JUST BECAUSE
OF THAT STINKING MONSTER.
YOUR FACE COULD HOLD
A THREE-DAY RAIN, BRUNO.
I PROMISE YOU THAT
HE'LL BE DESTROYED.
[BRUNO CRYING]
BUT GIVE ME TIME.
JUST A LITTLE TIME!
IT WON'T BE TOO LONG BEFORE
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR REVENGE.
LET ME GET THE FIRST
PLATE FIRST-- THE BRACELET!
LOOKS LIKE IT
SCABBED OVER NICELY.
... AND YET SO FAR,
BECAUSE I CAN'T TOUCH THEM.
IT IS TOO DANGEROUS
TO DO IT.
HE'LL WAKE UP IN AN INSTANT
AND DESTROY US.
SOUNDS OKAY TO ME.
BUT I'LL GET HIM BACK,
I SWEAR IT,
NO MATTER HOW LONG
IT TAKES ME.
YOU DEVILISH MUMMY!
HE LOOKS LIKE MR. FRENCH.
LINE.
COME ON, WE BETTER GO NOW.
WE'LL BE NEEDING
A LOT OF TIME
IF THE PLAN I HAVE IS
GOING TO WORK OUT.
ANYTHING YOU SAY.
CAN AND WILL BE
USED AGAINST YOU.
COME, FLORA.
WOW, A LOT OF GOOD ACTING
IN THAT SCENE.
JOEL, WHAT WAS THE POINT
OF THIS LITTLE, UH--
LITTLE SCENE HERE.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THEY WERE JUST
STAKING OUT A LOCATION
TO COME AND SHOOT HERE LATER
WHEN THEY HAD SOMETHING
MEANINGFUL TO DO.
- OH.
YOU KNOW,
I REALLY DID YOU, HON.
CAN I CALL YOU AGAIN?
THINK HE'LL KISS HER NOW OR WAIT
TILL HE GETS TO THE DOOR?
IT'S ALWAYS A BETTER POLICY
TO KISS ON THE STEPS.
- AH.
- OR BY THE CAR.
- OR UNDER THE CAR.
- OR ON THE MOUTH.
YOU'LL GO UP TO YOUR ROOM,
THEN YOU'LL GO TO SLEEP.
AND WHEN YOU AWAKEN,
YOU'LL ACT QUITE NORMALLY.
YOU WILL BE REFRESHED
AND INVIGORATED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU WON'T RECALL A THING.
NOW, WALK.
- LIKE AN EGYPTIAN.
- GO ON.
BRUNO, DO THAT THINK
WITH THE CAR HORN AGAIN.
I LOVE THAT BIT.
[IMITATING HORN HONKING]
HEH, SHE FALLS FOR IT
EVERY TIME.
♪♪
WE'VE DONE THIS SCENE
BEFORE, ONLY AT NIGHT.
- ♪ I FEEL PRETTY ♪
- WELL, GOOD MORNING.
- ♪ OH SO PRETTY ♪
- GOOD MORNING, SWEETHEART.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
VERY TIRED.
WE WERE WAITING DOWN HERE
TO HAVE BREAKFAST WITH YOU.
WE COULD BOTH EAT A HORSE.
BACON AND EGGS,
LIKE ALWAYS?
NOTHING FOR ME, MARIA.
I HAVE A TERRIBLE
HEADACHE, DEAR.
WHAT'S THAT YOU'VE GOT
ON YOUR GOWN?
IT'S ALL DIRTY.
LOOKS LIKE DEAD,
DRIED FLESH.
YOU'VE BEEN DOWN
IN THE CELLAR.
NO, SWEETHEART.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT LOOK AT YOUR SLIPPERS,
THEY'RE ALL MUDDY.
AND YOU PITTED OUT
YOUR GOWN.
COME ON, WHAT HAVE YOU
BEEN UP TO?
JUST CAVORTING WITH MUMMIES
ALL NIGHT.
IT'S FUNNY, THESE ARE NEW
SLIPPERS, I JUST BOUGHT THEM.
- AND NOW THEY'RE DIRTY.
- AND SO ARE YOU!
- I THINK YOU WENT OUT
LAST NIGHT.
NO.
AFTER I TOOK MY BATH,
I WENT TO BED
BECAUSE I WAS TIRED.
YES, BUT YOU GOT UP
LATER ON, DIDN'T YOU?
- I DID? NO.
- SHH! WHO'S THE KID?
YES, BECAUSE I WOKE UP
A COUPLE OF TIMES,
AND YOU WERE NOT
IN BED.
NO, YOU'RE MISTAKEN, DARLING.
- I ASSURE YOU...
- GET THAT KID OUT OF THERE.
YOU WENT OUT LAST NIGHT,
HONEST, MOM.
COME ON, LET'S FORGET THE WHOLE
THING FOR NOW, ALL RIGHT?
FLOYD LOOKS CONFUSED.
REMEMBER, SHE HAS
A GREAT IMAGINATION.
TELL ME, HAS YOUR
HEADACHE PASSED?
NO. I'M GOING TO
LIE DOWN FOR A WHILE.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
AND I DON'T LIKE THE SMELL
OF THIS CONVERSATION.
YOU CHILDREN GO ON
AND HAVE YOUR BREAKFAST.
YES, DADDY.
COME ON, PINACATE,
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
OH, BOY,
WHAT A LIAR YOU ARE!
YOU SHUT YOUR BIG MOUTH.
YOU'RE THE LIAR!
YOU CAN'T EVEN ACT YOURSELF
OUT OF A PAPER BAG.
YOU'LL NEVER WORK
IN CORAL GABLES AGAIN!
PINACATE,
I'M VERY WORRIED.
THIS ATTITUDE THAT
WE'VE OBSERVED IN FLORA
IS NOT NORMAL.
WHAT'S MORE, I'M AFRAID
THAT THE BAT
HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
MAYBE SHE SHOULD CHOKE UP
ON IT A LITTLE BIT.
THEN DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT CHILD WAS TELLING
THE TRUTH ABOUT IT,
AND THAT HER MOTHER GOT UP
AND WENT OUT?
YES, IT'S QUITE PROBABLE.
BUT FLORA INSISTED SHE DIDN'T
LEAVE HER BED FOR A SECOND.
BECAUSE SHE CAN'T
RECALL ANYTHING.
WHEN SHE GOT UP LAST NIGHT,
SHE WAS SLEEPING.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
IT SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I THINK.
SHE WAS HYPNOTIZED AND COULD BE
UNDER POSTHYPNOTIC SUGGESTION.
SO IT SEEMS TO ME
THAT THE BAT CONTROLS HER
FROM A DISTANCE.
- WITH SONAR.
- IT'S LOGICAL.
- WHAT A SLEUTH.
THIS STRANGE ATTITUDE
IN FLORA INDICATED
THAT UNSCRUPULOUS VILLAIN KRUPP
MADE HER LEAVE THE HOUSE
DURING THE NIGHT.
BUT WHERE DID THEY GO TO?
CAN'T YOU GUESS
WHAT HE'S TRYING TO DO?
NO.
YOU CERTAINLY KNOW WHAT HE'S
AFTER-- THE BREASTPLATE
AND BESIDES THAT,
THE BRACELET.
AND HE SNAPPY COCO CHANEL
PANTS SUIT.
THEN YOU THINK THAT
SHE WAS MADE
TO GO ALONG WITH KRUPP,
AND HE WANTED HER
TO GUIDE HIM
TO FIND THE MUMMY.
EXACTLY, AND YOU AND I
MUST GO THERE.
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT
IF THAT SCOUNDREL
STOLE THOSE OBJECTS.
BUT THAT'LL BE DIFFICULT.
YOU CAN'T INVESTIGATE
WITHOUT ANY CLUES.
FLOYD'S A GREAT BARBER, BUT NOT
A VERY GOOD DETECTIVE.
YES.
NEITHER OF THEM ARE
VERY GOOD ACTORS.
WELL, THAT GOES
WITHOUT SAYING.
HE SMOKES--
HE SMOKES VERY WELL, THOUGH.
IF LOVING YOU IS WRONG,
I DON'T WANT TO BE RIGHT.
SUPPOSE WE TOOK HER SLIPPERS
TO THE LABORATORY
TO HAVE THAT MUD ANALYZED.
THAT COULD HELP US
DON'T YOU THINK?
I CAN TELL YOU WHAT KIND
OF SLIPPERS THEY ARE.
YES, THAT MIGHT JUST BE
THE SOLUTION.
WE'LL TAKE THEM, BUT I DON'T
THINK SHE SHOULD FIND OUT.
WE'D BETTER DO IT ALL
IN SECRET.
- YEAH!
- COME ON.
SECRET!
WE'LL GET IN DISGUISE.
WE'LL BE WOMEN.
YES, NOW, I'M QUITE SURE.
IT'S EMBEDDED IN THE DIRT.
THEY'RE SLIPPERS.
OF COURSE, IT'S A SMALL
QUANTITY, DOCTOR,
BUT YOUR SUSPICIONS
ARE CORRECT--
THEY'RE PIECES OF MARBLE.
YOU'RE SURE IT'S MARBLE?
- MARBLE?
- CAN YOU IDENTIFY ITS SOURCE?
IS IT A SPECIAL KIND?
- NO, IT ISN'T.
BUT IT'S A FINE QUALITY.
- CLASSY.
- IT MIGHT BE A TARARE MARBLE.
- I CAN SAY THAT.
- MAYBE A...
IT'S USED IN THE CONSTRUCTION
OF MAUSOLEUMS, AS FAR AS I KNOW.
- THANK YOU.
- OH...
SHE WENT OUT LATE AT NIGHT
AND PLAYED MARBLES.
WHAT COULD IT MEAN?
MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE OTHER SET...
FORTUNATELY,
IT WAS STILL LIT.
THIS IS THE LAST CEMETERY.
WE'VE SEEN ALL THE OTHERS.
IF WE DON'T FIND
ANYTHING HERE,
WE'D BETTER FORGET ABOUT IT.
- HELLO THERE
- GOOD EVENING
WELL-ACTED, FLOYD.
TELL ME, ARE YOU
THE WATCHMAN HERE?
YES, SIR.
ANYTHING I CAN DO FOR YOU?
WHY YES, WE'D LIKE TO
ASK YOU A FEW QUESTIONS.
WE'D LIKE TO KNOW IF YOU'VE
SEEN ANYTHING STRANGE
THE LAST FEW WEEKS,
OR MORE RECENTLY.
ANYTHING VERY SUSPICIOUS
IN OR AROUND THE CEMETERY,
PERTAINING TO ONE
OF THE GRAVES.
- JUST THE FILM CREW.
- ARE YOU FROM THE POLICE?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT,
MY FRIEND,
AND WE'RE AFTER A VERY
DANGEROUS CRIMINAL,
WHOM WE SUSPECT HAS BEEN
HIDING ONE
OF THE CEMETERIES
AROUND THE CITY.
WELL, THE FACT IS, SOMETHING
PRETTY DOGGONE CURIOUS
DID HAPPEN.
JUST TWO NIGHTS AGO,
I WAS SURPRISED
TO RUN INTO A YOUNG WOMAN HERE
WEARING A KIND OF WHITE ROBE.
SHE SEEMED TO BE ASLEEP,
AND TWO MEN ENTERED
THE GROUNDS WITH HER.
HE'S NOT GONNA
FLASH BACK, IS HE?
WHEN I ASKED THEM
WHO THEY WERE,
ONE OF THE GUYS SLUGGED ME,
AND THEY LEFT ME OUT COLD
HERE ON THE GROUND.
HOW DO YOU THINK I GOT
THIS SWELL HAT?
THEN WE'LL BE TAKING A LOOK
AROUND THE GROUNDS.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING
YOU WANT.
- ANYTHING YOU WANT.
- YOU'RE THE POLICE.
DON'T TOUCH HIM, HE'S FILTHY.
YOU SEE, I WAS RIGHT.
AT LAST,
WE'RE ON THE TRAIL.
NOW THE TOUGH PART
HAS YET TO COME.
NO, YOU'RE ON MY FOOT.
'CAUSE WE'VE GOT TO
WALK AROUND
TILL WE FIND THE MUMMY.
LOOK, WE'D BETTER
SEPARATE NOW.
GO THAT WAY PINACATE.
I'LL GO OVER THERE.
- SEPARATE?
- BUT I LOVE YOU.
[A LA JERRY LEWIS]
OW, DEAN!
DON'T--
WOW--OW...
HEY, OH, DAD AND MUMMY
AND BRUNO!
♪♪
OH, VERY BAD.
OH!
OH, DINO?
OH, OH...
LIONS AND TIGERS AND OW!
[ALL IMITATING JERRY LEWIS,
OVERLAPPING DIALOGUE]
DINO?
HEY.
OH, OH, BEWARE,
ALL WHO ENTER, WHOA!
"M."
OH...
WHOA, DEAN?
DINO?
WHERE ARE YOU?
WOW.
[A LA BING CROSBY]
JERRY, JERRY, WHERE ARE YA?
I CAN'T FIND YA.
COME ON, JERRY,
WHERE ARE YA?
COME ON, SAY SOMETHING
TO ME, BOY.
DEAN, OVER HERE!
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
QUIT HORSING AROUND,
WE GOT A MUMMY TO FIND.
EDWARD, EDWARD,
COME HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- WE'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
- I'M GETTING OUT OF HERE.
WOW...JOL...
I HOPE THERE'S DOGS
IN HERE.
COME ON!
I JUST DON'T SEE IT
AT ALL, GUYS.
COME ON, CROW,
I THINK IT'LL WORK.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE OF US
WHO EVEN LOOKS A LITTLE BIT
LIKE ENOCH DID.
[DOGS YAPPING IN BACKGROUND]
NO, MY BROW'S ALL DIFFERENT.
I'M-- I'M JUST-- NO.
OH, IT'S THERE.
I SEE IT.
JOEL, BE SURE TO
WIPE DOWN HIS NOSE.
BOY, IF I WERE A DEMON DOG,
I'D JUST BOW DOWN
AN KNEEL AND BOW TO YOU.
I'M ALREADY STARTING
TO MISS THAT OLD ENOCH.
YOU KNOW, I ALMOST CRIED
WHEN HE LEFT.
JUST LIKE WHEN
OLD YELLER GOT SHOT.
OH, CROW, COME ON,
IT'LL BE EASY.
YOU GO OUT THERE,
YOU SAY TO THE DEMON DOGS,
"COME ONE, EVERYBODY,
LET'S GO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU."
YOU DUCK BACK IN.
IT'S EASY.
GREAT ADVICE COMING FROM
MR. FIREPLUG.
- HEY, WATCH IT, PAL.
- HEY...
HEY, TAKE IT EASY, YOU TWO,
LISTEN,
IF WORSE COMES TO WORST,
JUST TELL 'EM
THE SATELLITE OF LOVE IS
A GIANT CHICKEN BONE, OKAY?
YOU LOOK GREAT, NOW JUST GO
DO THE JOB, AND BE REGAL.
ALL RIGHT.
I LOOK LIKE CHARLIE MCCARTHY.
[DOGS YAPPING]
LET'S WATCH IT ON THE MONITOR.
[CROW]
ALL RIGHT, QUIET DOWN,
QUIET DOWN.
AHEM,
I AM ENOCH.
I AM YOUR LORD
AND CHARISMATIC LEADER.
REMEMBER?
AND, HEY, WHAT'S
THE LEASH LAW HERE?
- HEY!
- OH, HE'S GETTING IT.
HEY, HEY, CURB YOUR BUDDY
OVER THERE-- OH!
[BOTH GROANING]
[TOM LAUGHING]
KIND OF A WARM FEELING,
EH, CROW?
WELL, I THINK IT WENT
KINDA WELL, YOU KNOW?
THEY WERE EATING OUT
OF THE PALM OF MY HAND...
TILL I RAN OUT OF TREATS.
AND SPEAKING OF TREATS,
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪♪
THEY'RE IN THE CRYPT.
DEMON DOGS EVERYWHERE.
DUDE, IT'S SCARING ME.
YOU GOT ALL THAT STUFF
OFF YOU, CROW?
YES, I DID.
GREAT IDEA.
LOOK, THE BREASTPLATE
AND THE BRACELET.
THEY DIDN'T TAKE IT.
ALL THIS I'VE JUST TOLD YOU
OCCURRED FIVE YEARS AGO.
WE VISITED THE CRYPT
FROM TIME TO TIME
TO TAKE A LOOK
AT THE MUMMY,
WITH ITS BREASTPLATE
AND ITS BRACELET TOO.
AND THE SNAPPY
COCO CHANEL PANTS SUIT.
IS HE STILL AROUND?
YOU KNOW, HE DISAPPEARED
FROM SIGHT.
THEN, JUST A COUPLE
OF DAYS AGO,
WE READ AN ARTICLE
THAT IS VERY INTERESTING.
WE WERE PROFOUNDLY
SURPRISED BY IT.
ACCORDING THE THE ARTICLE,
A COUPLE OF NIGHTS BEFORE,
A CADAVER HAD BEEN ROBBED
FROM THE AMPHITHEATER.
ABRACADAVER?
AND THE INDIVIDUAL WHO DID IT
WAS THE BAT, OF COURSE.
YES. IN THE BEGINNING,
WE HAD SOME DOUBTS,
SINCE THE MAN
WHO HAD BEEN ATTACKED
COULDN'T OFFER US A DESCRIPTION
OF HIS ASSAILANTS.
BUT LATER ON,
OUR SUSPICIONS WERE CONFIRMED.
DON'T PLAY WITH THAT.
YESTERDAY THERE WAS A BURGLARY
IN THE RADIOLOGY INSTITUTE.
THE THIEVES TOOK A MACHINE
THAT USES RADIUM.
THEY ALSO STOLE A BRAIN
OUT OF A LABORATORY.
- ICK.
- EXCELLENT.
THIS TIME, THE POLICE
WERE ABLE
TO IDENTIFY THE CROOKS
AS THE BAT AND ALL HIS BAND.
WE'RE COVERING A PLOT HOLE
WITH ASPHALT HERE.
ARE THERE ANY
GOOD CLUES, DOCTOR?
LEAD IS THE ONLY METAL
CAPABLE OF RESISTING RADIATION.
LEAD MATERIAL
IN THIS CITY IS HANDLED
BY MANY WHOLESALERS.
AFTER VISITING THE FIRST
THREE OR FOUR...
THEY GOT TO THE RIGHT ONE.
- GOOD MORNING, SIR.
- GOOD MORNING.
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, GENTLEMEN?
WE'RE SORRY TO BE
A BOTHER TO YOU,
BUT IS IT JUST POSSIBLE
THAT LATELY
YOU SENT OUT A LARGE
SHIPMENT OF LEAD?
COULD YOU GIVE ME
THAT INFORMATION?
IN THE LAST TWO DAYS?
OR IT COULD BE A WEEK,
MORE OR LESS.
- LET ME CHECK.
- FIVE YEARS, MAYBE.
WE KEEP A RECORD
OF OUR SHIPMENTS IN THIS BOOK.
WHY, YES, WE SEND A LEAD BALLOON
TO THE WRITERS OF THIS FILM.
YES, HERE IT IS.
EXACTLY FIVE DAYS AGO
WE MADE DELIVERY
OF 20 PLATES OF LEAD SHIELDING,
FOUR INCHES IN WIDTH,
TO NUMBER 22 SHADE STREET.
TO A MAN CALLED, UH,
"THE BAT."
- MANY THANKS.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE TOLD US.
WE WERE INVESTIGATING
FOR DAYS.
AT LAST WE GOT
THE ADDRESS.
I THINK THE BAT HAD MADE
HIS HIDEOUT THERE,
OR HIS LABORATORY.
OR HIS NEST.
WELL, I DON'T SEE WHY
THIS THIEVING DR. KRUPP
WOULD GO TO THE EFFORT
OF STEALING RADIUM,
A COMPLETE HUMAN BRAIN,
AN ALSO THE BODY OF SOME MAN.
HE'S NUTS.
DO YOU RECALL THAT THE BAT
ONCE TOLD FLORA
THAT HE WAS WORKING
ON A NEW EXPERIMENT?
MM-HMM.
I THINK THAT IS
THE EXPLANATION.
- OH...
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBT THAT
DR. KRUPP AND HIS CRIMINALS
ARE PLANNING
TO CAUSE TROUBLE.
THAT'S WHAT CRIMINALS
DO BEST.
NOW I'LL TELL YOU WHY I CALLED
YOU HERE TONIGHT, GENTLEMEN--
BECAUSE YOU BOTH
ARE SCIENTISTS...
AND WE LIKE BORING STUFF.
JUST IN CASE WE END UP
BEING MURDERED
YOU MEAN TO SAY YOU TWO
ARE THINKING OF GOING THERE
WITHOUT TAKING
THE POLICE ALONG?
- YES, BECAUSE, YOU SEE,
WE'RE STILL NOT SURE
THAT THAT'S
THE BAT'S LABORATORY.
AND THE POLICE STILL DON'T HAVE
MUCH FAITH IN US
BECAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED
BEFORE.
THEY JUST NEED TO CHECK
FOR BAT DROPPINGS.
- FLORA...
- GUANO?
IN CASE WE'RE NOT
BACK HERE AT THE HOUSE
BY 3:00 IN THE MORNING,
I'M LEAVING IT UP TO YOU
TO CALL THE POLICE.
- EDWARD!
- SELL EVERYTHING.
- LET'S KISS.
- HEY, WATCH IT, WATCH IT!
- LIGHTS.
- LOOKS PAINFUL.
BETTY CROCKER
TEST KITCHENS.
LET'S SEE, ONE, TWO THREE.
OKAY, IT FORMS
THREE CREAMY LAYERS.
NO, WAIT, THREE LAYERS--
A CREAMY LAYER,
A GELATINOUS LAYER AND--
DAMN IT, I MUST FIND
THAT FORMULA!
♪♪
[LOW RUMBLING]
POP ROCKS SEEM TO ME
MOVING ALONG NICELY.
AND THOSE M&Ms ARE
ALMOST DONE.
OH, MY GOD, HE'S TORN APART
THE MICHELIN MAN.
BIF, BUDDY, IT'S US.
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
OH, HOW HORRIBLE HE EVEN
SLASHED HIS SPARE.
FREEZE, YOU TWO!
THIS LOOKS LIKE IT WAS SHOT
WITH A SECURITY CAMERA.
- OH, IT'S CRATER FACE.
- DR. ALMADA.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
- BRUNO?
- NO, KITTY CARLISLE!
WHO DID YOU THINK IT IS?
A SOUVENIR OF THE MUMMY.
THE BOSS IS GONNA BE
VERY HAPPY
TO SAY HELLO
TO YOU TWO AGAIN.
COME ALONG.
THIS IS THE KIND OF FILM
YOU WON'T PUT ON PAUSE
WHEN YOU LEAVE THE ROOM.
[THUNDER]
IT ENCOURAGES YOU TO GO
TO GET A SANDWICH.
- BOSS.
- KINDA LIKE TV REPELLENT.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND
OUT IN FRONT.
DR. ALMADA
AND HIS SHADOW.
THIS IS A PLEASANT
SURPRISE, GENTLEMEN.
- AFTER SUCH A LONG TIME...
- I'M NOT HIS SHADOW.
... I COME FACT TO FACE
WITH SUCH GOOD FRIENDS.
EXACTLY WHERE DID YOU
FIND THEM?
OUT IN THE SHOP THERE,
LOOKING AROUND.
- I OFFER YOU
MY CONGRATULATIONS,
BECAUSE YOU ARE
MAGNIFICENT DETECTIVES.
DID ANYONE ELSE
COME WITH THEM?
NOBODY ELSE.
I SAW THEM WHEN THEY DREW UP
IN THE AUTOMOBILE, ALONE.
BRUNO, AREN'T YOU GOING
TO ATTEND OUR GUESTS
THEY WAY THEY DESERVE?
GO FETCH CHAIRS
FOR THE GENTLEMEN.
SURE, RIGHT AWAY.
ELECTRIC CHAIRS.
TELL ME, HOW'S YOUR BEAUTIFUL
AND CHARMING WIFE, DR. ALMADA?
I LEARNED ABOUT
YOUR MARRIAGE,
AND I ADMIT IT'S
A BIT LATE TO SAY IT,
BUT RECEIVE
MY CONGRATULATIONS.
AND TAKE THIS TOASTER
AND FONDU SET AS A GIFT.
HOW ARE YOU THESE DAYS?
ARE YOU STILL
THE CHAMPION OF RIGHT?
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
AND I'M GLAD.
NO, I'M JUST A SHADOW,
JERK.
COME OVER HERE.
[THUNDER]
START THE MUSIC.
THEY'RE PLAYING
MUSICAL CHAIRS.
HOW HORRIBLE.
NEXT, THEY'LL BE PINNING
THE TAIL ON SOMEBODY.
[BOTH]
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT YOU'D BE HERE
AT THE MOMENT TO WITNESS THIS?
BECAUSE YOU'RE ABOUT
TO SEE SOMETHING
THAT WILL ASTONISH YOU--
TRULY UNBELIEVABLE.
[LAUGHS]
WHEN YOU FEAST YOUR EYES
ON THIS,
I DON'T DOUBT THAT
YOU'LL BE AMAZED, DOCTOR.
AND YOU'LL BE THE FIRST
TO CONGRATULATE ME!
BET IT'S A ROBOT.
FRANKLY, I'M HAPPY
THAT YOU CAME HERE
TO VISIT US,
DR. ALMADA.
YOU'RE A MAN WHO IS
BASICALLY AN INTELLECTUAL,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO UNDERSTAND...
BUT YOU HURT INSIDE.
... THE GREATNESS
OF MY INVENTION.
YOU'RE BASICALLY AN OVEREATER.
I THINK YOU REMEMBER
THAT TIME WE MET.
SINCE THEN, I'VE WORKED
DAY AND NIGHT,
WITHOUT RESTING
FOR A MINUTE.
AND DURING ALL THAT
HECTIC TIME,
I EXPLORED POWERS
THAT NO ONE ELSE KNOWS.
ALL THOSE GREAT MYSTERIES,
THE VERY BASIS OF CREATION.
THEN THAT MEANS THAT
YOU DEFY ALL THE LIMITS
THAT WERE PUT DOWN
BY GOD.
EHH, MAYBE.
THERE ARE CERTAIN SECRETS
THAT WE COULD EXPLORE
AND DISCOVER RAPIDLY.
I'M JUST TOYING
WITH GOD'S LAWS.
AND THAT'S WHY
IT'S SUCH A SHAME
THAT FEAR IMPEDES US SO,
DR. ALMADA.
YOU'RE COMPLETELY MAD,
AND IGNORANT ALSO.
[ALL]
THANK YOU.
EVERY MAD SCIENTIST HAS
ONE OF THESE SPEECHES.
[THUNDER]
DON'T YOU RESPECT
RESEARCH AT ALL?
DON'T YOU WANT TO LEAR TO KNOW
WHY A BODY FUNCTIONS?
I DO, AND AT LAST
I FOUND THE CAUSE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS HEART
THAT'S BEATING.
IT LIVES!
IT LIVES AND PULSATES
BECAUSE I GAVE IT LIFE,
AND IF I CAN GIVE LIFE...
DOESN'T HAVE VERY GOOD
RHYTHM, THOUGH.
... WHY CAN'T I GIVE IT
TO THE BODIES
THAT ARE DAMNED TO DEATH
AND DECAY?
AND WHY CAN'T YOU GIVE IT
TO THE SCRIPT?
NO ONE CAN POSSIBLY IMAGINE
HOW I WORKED
WHEN I DUG IN THE MUD
WITH THESE HANDS
AND ENTERED TOMBS.
I TORTURED MANY ANIMALS
WITH PLEASURE
TO FIND THE ANSWERS...
REMEMBER THE UNFORTUNATE
PUSH ME/PULL YOU.
YOU'RE INSANE, DO YOU KNOW?
[TOM]
YES!
I DECIDE TO CREATE A MAN.
A BREATHING BODY--
A REAL MAN!
AND I HAVE MADE
THAT DREAM COME TRUE.
THERE YOU HAVE THE GREATEST...
[ALL] YAY!
- COOL.
- A HUMAN ROBOT, DOCTOR.
[THUNDER]
TONIGHT I'M GOING
TO FIND OUT.
TONIGHT I'M GOING TO PUT IT
TO THE SUPREME TEST.
THE "COSMO"
SEX QUIZ?
I'LL ACTIVATE THE CREATURE.
BUT THIS IS MONSTROUS,
DOCTOR!
IF IT LIVES, THEN MY TRIUMPH
WILL BE COMPLETE, DR. ALMADA.
BECAUSE I'LL GET THE TREASURE,
AND I'LL BE RICH!
[JOEL]
SHUT UP.
THIS THING I CREATED
HAS ENORMOUS POWER.
AND YOU'LL WATCH IT!
NOW, THEN,
LIFE FOR THE ROBOT!
THE ONLY THIN DIABOLICAL
ABOUT THIS GUY IS HIS ACTING.
DOCTOR, WATCH THIS!
[THUNDER]
THAT WOULD MAKE A REALLY
EXCELLENT MINIATURE GOLF COURSE.
[TOM]
DO I DETECT A THEME?
[JOEL]
I JUST-- I DON'T KNOW, I'M...
[CROW]
ROBOT, YAY!
I'M JUST SEEING
MINIATURE GOLF COURSES.
COOL.
WHO'S GOT THE LINE?
LINE, PLEASE.
[THUNDER]
DON'T YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE BETTER--
ROBOT, SCARFACE, LIGHT BULB,
FLOYD...
ROBOT, DOCTOR,
GOOD SHOT OF ME.
DO YOU HAVE ANY JUMPER CABLES
IN YOUR CAR OR SOMETHING?
IT'S NOT WORKING.
2:30 ALREADY.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE BETTER
TO CALL THE POLICE NOW?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- PICK UP THE PHONE AND DIAL.
NO, LET'S ALL WAIT
TILL 3:00 A.M.
AND RESPECT
THE DOCTOR'S WISHES.
SUPPOSE THEY'RE IN DANGER?
[MACHINE TRILLING}
[THUNDER]
[CROW]
ANOTHER GOOD SHOT OF ME.
[TOM]
GOOD SHOT OF THE ROBOT.
NOBODY'S MOVING.
[THUNDER]
I... THINK THAT'S
A DIFFERENT EMOTION, THOUGH.
TABLE'S MOVING.
THE TABLE'S A BETTER ACTOR
THAN ANYONE.
THEY'RE ALL MADE OUT
OF THE SAME MATERIAL... WOOD.
[BEEPING]
[CROW]
SOMEBODY MOVE.
LAUGH OR SOMETHING.
SQUEEZE IT OUT.
COME ON, FLOYD.
BRUNO?
[TOM AND CROW]
ROBOT?
♪ CHAIN CHAIN CHAIN ♪
[JOEL]
HE'S SO POWERFUL.
[LAUGHING]
YOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY?
OH, THIS IS GREAT,
DOCTOR!
THE GREATEST INVENTION!
[LAUGHING]
SINCE THE COFFEE MAKER.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
COULD HAVE HAPPENED TO YOU?
IT'S NOT SO GREAT,
IT DOESN'T HAVE KNEES.
[TOM]
YOU CAN SEE IT STANDING THERE.
YOU CAN SEE IT
STANDING THERE!
A MARVELOUS MACHINE.
A TRIBUTE TO THE GREAT
INTELLIGENCE OF MAN!
A HUMAN ROBOT.
WITH THIS SHINY CREATURE,
NO HUMAN BEING ON THIS EARTH
CAN OPPOSE ME!
WAIT A "HUMAN ROBOT"?
THERE'S A FLAW RIGHT THERE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO YOU RIGHT NOW?
[CROW]
ONLY BITS OF IT ARE HUMAN.
HAD I NOT DIMINISHED
THE ELECTRIC FORCE,
THE CURRENT
THAT MAKES HIM MOVE
AND THAT IS CONTAINED
IN THIS APPARATUS?
WITH THE SLIGHTEST TWIST
OF THIS DIAL...
FLOYD IS STUNNED.
YOU TOO WOULD HAVE BEEN
CONVERTED
INTO ATOMIC DUST
INSTANTANEOUSLY!
BECAUSE THE ROBOT
UTILIZES RADIUM,
AND HAS SUFFICIENT POWER
TO DISINTEGRATE
ANYTHING IN THE WORLD!
TONIGHT IT MEETS THE MUMMY.
BRUNO, PREPARE
THE SPECIAL PLATES.
THE LEAD WILL SHIELD
MY TRUCK.
[JOEL]
BRING THE GOOD CHINA.
HURRY, TIME IS FLYING!
TONIGHT MY ROBOT HAS
TO MAKE A VISIT, YOU KNOW,
IN A CERTAIN CEMETERY.
- RAPID OIL CHANGE.
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
TEN MINUTES TO 3:00.
I TOLD YOU, THERE'S NO TIME
TO LOSE, BRUNO!
WE HAVE A COMMERCIAL.
TOODLES.
[LAUGHING]
♪♪
I WANT THE POLICE.
IT'S URGENT.
[JOEL DOES SILLY,
INDISTINCT VOICE]
HEADQUARTERS, I WANT TO TALK
TO THE CHIEF OF POLICE.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
3:00, AND ALL'S HELL.
I WANT YOU TO STOP
AND THINK ABOUT THIS.
A NEW KIND OF WORLD.
AN ARMY OF ROBOTS OBEYING ME.
HEY, LOOK, WE GOT
THE POINT, BUT--
THIS IS GREAT--
WE GOTTA GO, OKAY?
SHEEP OBEYING MY ORDERS.
A NEW THEORY THAT MAN
HAS NOT DARED IMAGINE!
THAT WOULD MAKE YOU
A SHEPHERD.
I'LL MAKE SOME MORE.
MAYBE 1,000.
NOW THAT I KNOW HOW,
THE REST IS EASY.
OH, YOU'RE TOO LOW.
GO A MILLION.
THE TREASURE OF THE AZTECS!
THAT'S WHY TONIGHT, THE MUMMY
WILL GIVE ME WHAT I WANT!
[JOEL]
CORN?
- IT'S ALL SET.
- THIS GUY SNAPPED A TWIG.
- FINE.
- I THINK THE WHOLE BRANCH
CAME DOWN.
- ... AND GUARD
OUR DISTINGUISHED FRIENDS.
THEY, MUSTN'T GET AWAY.
THEY'RE AN EXTREMELY IMPORTANT
COG IN MY PLAN.
GREAT, FIRST I'M A SHADOW
NOW I'M A COG.
BUT YOU'D ONLY
GET UNDERFOOT.
WRIGHT'S GOTTA TAKE
MEDICINE EVERY TWO HOURS,
CAN HE GO?
... I COULD DESTROY
THE MUMMY.
AND WITH THE GOLD BREASTPLATE
AND BRACELET IN MY HANDS,
YOU BEGAN ONCE MORE
TO TRANSLATE THE
HIEROGLYPHICS.
GEEZ, IS HE LONG-WINDED.
THIS TIME YOU'RE HELPLESS
BECAUSE NO ONE KNOWS
YOU'RE HERE.
SHUT UP!
DR. ALMADA.
[LAUGHS]
TIME FOR BRUNO'S
ELECTROLYSIS.
[BEEPING COMING FROM
ROBOT]
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO?
- UH, HE'S GOING TO PAT
HIS PART.
- GITCHEE GITCHEE GOO
DICK YORK AS
THE MUMMY.
NO, THAT'S THE ROBOT.
OH, THE ROBOT, SORRY.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE
DICK SARGENT ANYWAY.
♪ I'M MILTON YOUR
BRAND NEW SON ♪
♪ PUT YOUR RIGHT FOOT IN ♪
♪ YOU PUT YOUR RIGHT
FOOT OUT ♪
♪ YOU DO THE ROBEY POKEY ♪
♪ AND YOU TURN
YOURSELF ABOUT ♪
♪ YOUR HEAD IS FILLED
WITH ELECTRODES ♪
♪ IT MAKES YOU
WANT TO SHOUT ♪
♪ AND THAT'S WHAT
IT'S ALL ABOUT ♪
HEY.
♪ RIGHT FOOT IN ♪
- I DON'T HAVE ANY
FEET, JOEL.
- OH.
THE FUN'S OVER.
OH, WE'RE TO
THE NEW PLACE.
LET'S HURRY, I'M
AFRAID FOR THEIR LIVES.
YOU'RE AFRAID FOR
YOUR LIVES?
I'M AFRAID FOR
YOUR CAREER.
YOU CALL THAT A CAREER?
YOU KNOW I CAN'T HELP
BUT THINK THAT ROBOT
WOULD BE EXCELLENT
ON A MINIATURE GOLF COURSE.
STOP IT.
LOOKS LIKE A COFFEE MAKER.
KRUPPS COFFEE MAKER
OH, NO.
SORRY.
[GROANING, GUNSHOT]
WAY TO GO.
OH, UH, OH.
♪ UH-HUH, THIS IS
FOR ANDY ♪
CAN YOU DO YOU
FLOYD VOICE?
HUH, YES. HUH, YES.
- OH, THE ROBOT'S VERY--
- ALL RIGHT, FLOYD, FLOYD,
HEY, CUT IT OUT.
THAT'S FOR AUNT BEA.
THAT'S FOR OPIE.
THAT'S FOR GOOBER.
UH, OW.
WHERE'RE MY GLASSES?
WHERE ARE MY GLASSES?
THEY'RE ON YOUR FACE.
THERE THEY ARE.
HUH, YES.
OH, YES.
GREAT COMIC ACTOR.
POOR, BIP, THE MISSION MAN.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
CHIEF YOU CAN ARREST
THOSE TWO MEN THERE
IN THE OTHER ROOM.
COME ON.
DOCTOR, THE BAT HAS
GONE TO THE TOMB
WHERE THE MUMMY IS.
LET'S HURRY, THERE'S
NO TIME TO LOSE.
[ROBOT BEEPING]
WHAT'S THAT?
A MAN MADE OUT
OF TIN.
HUH, YES.
HEY, GUYS, GUESS WHO'S
HISTORY IN THIS SCENE?
JUAN VALDEZ.
BINGO.
YEAH.
USE THE ROBOT.
I'LL MURDERLIZE HIM.
LET'S SEE, I'LL PUT
THIS ON BROIL.
IT'S A DECOY.
[HISSING]
AH!
- [SCREAMING]
- MUST'VE BEEN A
SMOKING JACKET.
WELL, EMULATION IS THE
SINCEREST FORM OF FLATTERY.
I READ THAT IN A BOOK.
[ROBOT BEEPING]
♪♪
HURRY, BRUNO.
TAKE THE BREASTPLATE
AND BRACELET OFF OF HIM.
YES.
WELL, I THINK WE'RE
ABOUT TO SEE
THE NAMESAKE OF
THIS MOVIE.
THE ROBOT VS.
THE MUMMY.
I'M IN FOR TWENTY
ON THE ROBOT.
I DON'T KNOW, THAT MUMMY'S
GOT REAL NICE SPEED.
AMAZING SNAKE-LIKE
ACCURACY, TOO.
HE DOES A HELL
OF A SOFT SHOE, TOO.
HE'S THE AZTEC OF
A THOUSAND-AND-ONE HOLES.
THIS SCENE IS CLOSE CAPTIONED
FOR THE SPEED IMPAIRED.
HE MOVES LIKE GEORGE BURNS.
HE'LL PUT YOU IN
THE SLEEPER HOLD
IF HE JUST BREATHES
ON YOU.
THIS WHOLE MOVIE'S
A SLEEPER HOLD.
TAKE TWO OF THESE
AND A GLASS OF WATER
AND YOU'LL SLEEP
LIKE A BABY.
I COULDN'T TAKE
TWO OF THESE.
[GROWLING]
THIS ONE FEELS LIKE
A SUPPOSITORY.
LET'S KISS.
IT'S LIKE PROFESSIONAL
WRESTLING IN SLOW MOTION.
LIKE PROFESSIONAL ACTING
IN SLOW MOTION, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT IF
THE BAT WAS TRYING
TO FOOL EVERYBODY
AND HE'S JUST GOT A GUY
IN A SUIT, IT'S NOT REALLY
A ROBOT AT ALL.
THAT COULDN'T HAPPEN.
MAKES YOU THINK, THOUGH.
I DON'T KNOW, ONCE THAT
ROBOT GETS INTO GEAR,
YOU'RE REALLY GOING
TO SEE HIM KICK
SOME AZTEC.
HOO-HOO.
HUH-HO.
WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU HADN'T COUNTED ON.
ALL MUMMMIES
CARRY PLIERS.
HE DIDN'T GIVE MUCH
OF A FIGHT AT ALL.
OH, MUMMY, HOLD ME.
I THINK IT'S REALLY THE HUMAN
PART OF HIM THAT'S FAILING.
WELL THE HUMAN SIDE
LIKES THE RICH TASTE,
BUT THE ROBOT IN HIM LOVES
THE FROSTY GOODNESS.
OH, THIS ISN'T
A SERIAL, IS IT?
OH, YEAH, THE OTHER ONE
WAS A SERIAL.
OH, HOLD ME.
JOEL, RIGHT IN
THE ADAM'S APPLE.
[GUN FIRES]
[MUMMY GROWLS]
I LOOKED UP ANTI-CLIMAX
IN THE DICTIONARY
AND IT SAID SEE
"AZTEC MUMMY."
- THEY CONSTIPATED THE--
- NO THAT LOOKS REAL.
YEAH, I THINK THAT'S REAL.
I DIDN'T KNOW BILLY
BARTY WAS IN THIS.
[SCREAMS]
HE'S GOT A SMALL PART.
AHH!
THOSE TWO HAD TO DIE.
THANK GOD FLORA'S HERE.
POPOCA, IN MEMORY OF
THE GREAT LOVE
THAT ONCE EXISTED
BETWEEN US.
OH, HONEY.
BEFORE YOUR SKIN
WENT BAD.
... YOURS TO GUARD,
AND GO BACK TO THE GRAVE
OF OUR ANCESTORS WHERE WE
SHOULD NEVER HAVE INTERRUPTED
- YOUR ETERNAL SLEEP.
- AND NEVER DARKEN THIS
FILM AGAIN.
JOEL, ISN'T THAT
A DEMON DOG?
DEMON DOG?
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[DOG GROWLS]
[DOG CONTINUES GROWLING]
OH, MAN.
THIS ISN'T WORKING.
THIS IS GREAT, WHAT DO
WE DO NOW?
NO, I CAN SEE CLEARLY
THAT WHAT HOW WE'RE DEALING
WITH THESE THINGS
JUST ISN'T GOING TO WORK.
NO WAY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TRY
TO REVIEW THE MOVIE.
OUCH, INCOMING.
WHOA, I THOUGHT THAT A ROBOT
WITH A HUMAN HEAD
WAS REALLY OFFENSIVE.
- AH!
- YEAH, MYSTIC MANIA,
IT'S OBVIOUSLY WHY A LOT
OF THEM ARE FLYING US,
PROBABLY COMING
A MILE A WAY,
LET'S CRUSH.
I CAN SEE NOW THAT
THIS COMPLETELY
ISN'T WORKING, WE GOT
TO GET RID OF THESE THINGS
QUICK, CHECK YOUR FILES.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF
GAME BURGERS.
YEAH, NEWSPAPERS TOO.
WHICH WHAT GETS A DOG
GOING ON EARTH.
WELL, UH, CHASING RABBITS,
TICKS, CARS,
LICKING, SCRATCHING,
UH, TENNIS BALLS, UH...
- THAT'S IT, TENNIS BALLS.
- TENNIS BALLS?
LISTEN, GO DOWN TO THE
SERVICE POD,
FIND THE THRUSTERS
OFF OF 33A,
ATTACH THEM TO THAT
BIG DISPOSABLE BALL,
SHAPED LIKE A GIANT BALL.
WE'LL PUSH IT OUT
THE BAY PORT DOORS.
GO DOWN THERE,
KEEP YOUR FINGERS CROSSED
IF YOU GOT THEM.
OKAY, CAMBOT, PUT ME
ON EXTERIOR.
PUT IN FETCH MODE
ON MY MARK, NOW.
[DOGS BARKING]
[BARKING FADES]
- ALL RIGHT, THEY'RE GONE.
- [LAUGHS]
OH, JOEL, I DON'T WANT
TO BE A KILLJOY,
BUT DOESN'T "FETCH" MEAN
GO GET AND BRING BACK?
[ALL THREE]
OH!
THAT'S THE END
OF OUR EXPERIMENT,
I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY.
OH, I'M HAPPY.
ARE YOU, HAPPY?
I'M HAPPY.
GOOD, FILE THIS.
WELL, UNTIL NEXT TIME
MY LITTLE SQUARE PUDDING.